<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<OAI-PMH xmlns="http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/2.0/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/2.0/          http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/2.0/OAI-PMH.xsd">
  <responseDate>2012-05-15T03:24:18Z</responseDate>
  <request verb="ListRecords" metadataPrefix="rif" set="group:Australian%20Research%20Council">http://services.ands.org.au/home/orca/services/oai.php</request>
  <ListRecords>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561389</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561389</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561389</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence in Antimatter-Matter Studies</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-595489</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">ATOMIC AND MOLECULAR PHYSICS; NUCLEAR AND PARTICLE PHYSICS; PLASMA PHYSICS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof SJ Buckman; Dr JP Sullivan; Dr JC Lower; Prof RP McEachran; Prof I Bray; Prof AT Stelbovics; Dr D Fursa; Dr MJ Brunger; Prof PJ Teubner; Dr A Hill; Dr TJ Bastow; Prof B Lohmann; Prof JF Williams; Dr S Samarin; Dr SV Smith; Dr L Vance; Prof NJ Mason; Prof CM Surko; Ms JP Marler; Dr TN Rescigno; Prof CW McCurdy; Prof AE Orel; Em/Prof PD Burrow; A/Prof Y Nagai; Prof KR Bartschat; Dr H Koller; Mr SJ Pas
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 10,500,000.00
Application Year: 2004
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">While our world is made of matter, all particles have anti-particles and the most abundant is the positron, the electron's antiparticle.  It is the "workshop" for most anti-matter studies, particularly for the characterization of materials, including gases, polymers, insulators, thin films and surfaces, as well as the development of new and novel, nano-structured materials.  The ARC Centre of Excellence in Antimatter-Matter Studies (CAMS) will bring together key Australian and international scientists to work in this emerging scientific field of antimatter-matter interactions.  It will forge a unique and effective scientific team for state-of-the-art studies of the nano-world that underlies many everyday processes and new technologies.</description>
      <description type="brief">The Centre of Excellence in Antimatter-Matter Studies (CAMS) will develop tools and techniques to lead Australia into a new and exciting area of research in the physical, chemical and biological sciences. Pre-eminent Australian and international scientists will explore antimatter-matter interactions, in fundamental and applied fields, so that Australia maintains an international role in this emerging field. All particles have anti-particles of which the most abundant is the positron, the electron's antiparticle. The positron is the "workshop" for most anti-matter studies and we shall use it to characterize nanoscale materials, including gases, polymers, insulators, thin films and surfaces, and to develop novel, nanostructured materials.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348245</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348245</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348245</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre for Nanostructured Electromaterials 14</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-464691</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">PHYSICAL CHEMISTRY (INCL. STRUCTURAL)</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof GG WallaceProf SX DouProf HK LiuProf LA Kane-MaguireA/Prof GM SpinksA/Prof WE PriceProf SG PyneProf DR MacFarlaneDr M ForsythProf AM BondDr L SpicciaDr Y ChengProf GM ClarkDr GF SwiegersDr W HumphriesDr A HillProf Dr L DaiProf DL Officer
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 7,306,885.00
Application Year: 2002
First Year: 2003
</description>
      <description type="brief">Electromaterials transport electrons or ions and facilitate charge transfer, underpinning most energy capture/storage processes and cell communication. We propose a national Centre to develop nanostructured electromaterials with exceptional properties. The Centre aims to synthesise novel nanomaterials and assemble them into innovative nanoscale devices. We will exploit these materials to enhance performance in energy conversion/storage systems (eg. photovoltaics, batteries, including wearable systems), and novel energy transfer in bioapplications (eg. Bionic Ear). These advances, together with the resource of trained personnel, will assist Australian industry to exploit this exciting area.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882568</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882568</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882568</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Internecine conflict and violence in NSW Aboriginal communities: an historicised assessment of governance and social control</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593941</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">SOCIAL WORK</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms VL Grieves; Dr G Macdonald; Prof VJ Atkinson
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 200,000.00
Application Year: 2007
First Year: 2008
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Analysis of the context of conflict and violence in NSW Aboriginal communities through ethnohistoriographical techniques and Indigenous knowledge methodologies, including Aboriginal focus groups, will engage and empower Aboriginal people in innovative approaches to restoring social order. Research outcomes, specific to localities in NSW, have benefits for dealing with conflict and violence in Indigenous communities in Australia and internationally. Research outcomes will clarify the sources of conflict, ensure conflict resolution and ongoing civil societies, enhance the cultural viability of communities, and inform public developments with appropriate governance models, enhancing Indigenous wellbeing.</description>
      <description type="brief">Incidents of conflict and violence in NSW Aboriginal communities will be placed within the context of an analysis of existing literature and Australia-wide overview, local and regional ethnohistories, focus groups and interviews with representatives of local Aboriginal groups, government agencies, and other stakeholders. Permission from five representative localities in NSW will be secured for collaborative research and fieldwork. Focus groups of Aboriginal people as experts on conflict and violence in their communities will be established and research findings will be shared. This research process will clarify sources of conflict, deflect ongoing conflicts and inform public policy and Indigenous governance development.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0454365</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0454365</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0454365</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Unlocking Indigenous Students' full potential: A critical analysis of Indigenous students' aspirations</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-485355</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">EDUCATION STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr A Parente; A/Prof RG Craven
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 46,444.00
Application Year: 2003
First Year: 2004
</description>
      <description type="brief">Indigenous students' aspirations are significantly lower in comparison to non-Indigenous peers. Given the vital importance of aspirations for predicating life opportunities this is of dire concern. Utilising a synergistic blend of quantitative and qualitative research methodology this investigation aims to identify factors that positively and negatively impact on Indigenous students setting and achieving their aspirations, and test whether the pattern of relations between identified factors and aspirations differentially varies for Indigenous and non-Indigenous students. The project will also demonstrate the reliability of important measurement instruments for Indigenous populations and distinguish effective theoretical orientations and research methodology.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882245</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882245</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882245</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Reconciliation game: Australian Football in the new South Africa</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-507067</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">CULTURAL STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr BA Judd
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 170,648.00
Application Year: 2007
First Year: 2008
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">An understanding of the role sport has played in shaping settler/native relationships will enable Australia to support the development of enduring and meaning football contacts with post-Apartheid South Africa.  These will be built on appraisals that admit a similar colonial inheritance to sport in South Africa. Recent embrace of Indigenous Australian participation in Australian Football indicates the possibility of reconciliation and the potential for positive sporting interchange with post-Apartheid South Africa.  This study examines how reconciliations through Australia - South Africa sporting dialogue can not only be promoted but realised in terms of developing sustained and socially meaningful engagements. </description>
      <description type="brief">The Project critically investigates the Australian Football League's claims that the importation of Australian Football into the new South Africa will strengthen cross-racial reconciliation within that country. Touring Indigenous Australian teams have promoted the reconciliatory power of Australian Football, as a code untainted by a history of colonial racism and discrimination. The promotion of Australian Football as beyond race contrasts heavily with Rugby and Soccer as games inextricably linked to the politics of Apartheid in South Africa. This Project will examine the potential for Australian Football to offer a sporting dialogue capable of assisting reconciliation in post-Apartheid South Africa.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348212</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348212</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348212</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence for Integrative Legume Research</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-460867</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">GENETICS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof PM GresshoffProf BG RolfeA/Prof MB SinghA/Prof RJ RoseDr BJ CarrollDr CA BeveridgeDr U MathesiusDr MA DjordjevicA/Prof PL BhallaDr GF WeillerProf CR Parish
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Application Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">Legumes are essential for environmental sustainability and are important for maintaining human health. The Centre combines innovative genomic approaches to investigate the causal phenotypic links required for regulation of legume growth. The unique coexistence of multiple pluripotent meristems in shoots, roots, flowers and nodules permits the discovery of new paradigms governing legume architecture, reproductive differentiation and root-nodule development. New knowledge of the plant growth processes through mechanistic analysis of organ induction provides the tools to optimise the legume's productivity, quality, and environment adaptation.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0237862</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0237862</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0237862</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">BLACKMAN / WAIJIN - Facts, Fears and Fallacy - Relationships between Aboriginal Men and white women</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-565275</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">CULTURAL STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr J Maynard Dr V Haskins Dr HM Carey
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 27,000.00
Application Year: 2001
First Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">This pilot project aims to investigate archival records relating to the interpersonal relationships between Aboriginal men and white women. There has been much written and researched regarding the relationships between white men and Aboriginal women, including studies of the role and abuse of Aboriginal women in the stock industry and the maltreatment endured by Aboriginal girls taken from their families and indentured out into the apprenticeship scheme. However, this study aims to research the reverse subject; that is relationships between Aboriginal men and white women. The outcome is intended not only to be a contribution to historical scholarship, but also to the contemporary debates on issues surrounding reconciliation, gender, inter-marriage and colonialism.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775798</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775798</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775798</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">A Documentation and Multi-Method Critical Analysis of Ngarabal and Biripi Elders' Perspectives and Experiences of Australian History.</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-485355</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">OTHER STUDIES IN HUMAN SOCIETY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Miss F Blacklock; Prof RG Craven; Dr GE Munns
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 55,000.00
Application Year: 2006
First Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">The proposed research will add a fresh historical study by an Indigenous researcher to the literature by undertaking a multi-method critical analysis of Ngarabal and Biripi Elders' perspectives and experiences of Australian history. There are not many Elders left in my family and I believe that it is important for their stories to be told to the wider community and also as a record for the younger generation of my family to have as a tribute to our people. The significantly different life that Indigenous people have lived will contribute to an interesting and engaging public history.  </description>
      <description type="brief">My research will form a significant contribution to the Ngarabal and Biripi people as there has been very little research into our history. The research aims to make a significant contribution to the documentation of Australian history and the impact of this history on current government policies and community attitudes from an Indigenous perspective to ensure Indigenous historical interpretations and perspectives are voiced. Outcomes of my research will be comprehensive multi method critical analysis of the Ngarabal and Biripi people's history. The research will contain oral histories recorded by me with my Elders together with historical photographs, maps and documentation of significant places of interest.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0347845</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0347845</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0347845</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Cultural continuity and change at Shark Bay, Western Australia: an anthopological and historical study of the Malagana Aboriginal people.</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-464686</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">HISTORICAL STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms DJ Oxenham Prof DS Trigger Prof S Bowdler
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 10,000.00
Application Year: 2002
First Year: 2003
</description>
      <description type="brief">This project considers issues of cultural change, continuity and identity as they arise from the historical foundations of Shark Bay's present day community in Western Australia. It examines the ways in which Indigenous customary practices continue among the Malgana people, and how connection to sea and country remains an important facet of life. Drawing upon archaeological, historical and ethnographic materials, this project will produce an original account of changing patterns of identification with Aboriginal cultural heritage in an Indigenous community. The study will encompass relations between Malgana people and others who have historically come to live in the area.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775800</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775800</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775800</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Analysis of the effectiveness of a Quality Teaching framework in increasing Aboriginal students' educational outcomes</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-565275</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">OTHER STUDIES IN HUMAN SOCIETY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr M Donovan
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 60,000.00
Application Year: 2006
First Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This research will address key elements of the National research priority goals, including Priority 2 &amp; Priority 3 Promoting an innovation culture and economy. This research will make a significant contribution to educators' understanding of ways of increasing Aboriginal students' educational success rates. It will enhance the schooling experiences of Aboriginal students and provide teachers with the tools to engage with Aboriginal students in a culturally appropriate and educationally efficacious manner.  Improvement in Aboriginal students' educational qualifications will support welfare reform agendas, as higher educational attainment is associated with decreased welfare dependence, which is desired by Indigenous communities and leaders.</description>
      <description type="brief">The aim of this project is to analyse the effectiveness of the NSW Quality Teaching framework in increasing educational outcomes for Aboriginal students. The NSW Quality Teaching framework will be compared to Aboriginal pedagogical models to discern the similarities between these structures that contribute to successful outcomes for Aboriginal students. This research will identify teaching practices that support Indigenous styles of learning and will result in academic publications as well as pedagogical materials for use in schools and Indigenous communities.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561607</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561607</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561607</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence for Free Radical Chemistry and Biotechnology</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593909</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">ORGANIC CHEMISTRY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof CH Schiesser; Prof CJ Easton; Prof L Radom; Prof JA Angus; Dr MJ Davies; Prof PJ Scammells; Dr RA O'Hair; Dr ML Coote; Dr SE Bottle; Dr U Wille; Prof WR Jackson; Dr MS Sherburn; Dr PJ Barker; Dr E Rizzardo; Prof B Jarrott; Mr CH Such; Adj/Prof PJ Rogers
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 21,800,000.00
Application Year: 2004
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Free radical chemistry is of increasing importance in the manufacture of improved plastics, paints and related materials, in helping restrict oxidative processes that can lead to adverse human health and also to the degradation of important industrial materials.  The research will contribute to promoting &amp; maintaining good health by developing new methods for reducing the impacts of ageing as well as in the treatment of several life-threatening conditions such as stroke.  Industrial applications include better surface coatings for preserving metals, and additives to improve the quality and shelf life of beer and wines.</description>
      <description type="brief">Free radical chemistry plays a crucial role in important processes that affect the manufacturing industry, the environment, human health and animal health. The aim of this Centre is to develop new methods of radical generation and explore new reactions of synthetic significance involving radicals, including novel polymerisation processes. In addition, the increased understanding of free-radical chemistry gained through the research carried out in the Centre will be used to develop new biotechnology initiatives, including pharmaceutical products and antioxidants that will defend against oxidative stress associated with several diseases, as well as the degradation of industrial materials.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348177</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:58Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348177</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348177</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre for Perceptive and Intelligent Machines in Complex Environments</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-507067</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE AND SIGNAL AND IMAGE PROCESSING</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof RA JarvisA/Prof L KleemanA/Prof RA RussellA/Prof D SuterDr DL MorganA/Prof I ZukermanProf S VenkateshProf GA WestProf MV SrinivasanA/Prof AM MoffatProf LS SterlingA/Prof PJ StuckeyProf R KotagiriProf Y ShiraiProf B ShiraziDr H WangProf TM Caelli
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 5,625,165.00
Application Year: 2002
First Year: 2003
</description>
      <description type="brief">The Centre for Perceptive and Intelligent Machines in Complex Environments will perform fundamental research into and construct reliable large-scale systems of networked sensors, computational intelligence, mobile robots, and knowledge sources to support a large variety of critical human tasks, including surveillance/ security (eg. borders/airports/homes), health care support (eg. smart houses/ health condition monitoring, semi autonomous wheelchairs), and civil disaster support (eg. fighting bushfires, looking for people in rubble) always keeping people in the loop so that strong human/ machine cooperative ventures can achieve what neither human or machines could accomplish independently.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561435</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561435</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561435</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence for Coral Reef Studies</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-642603</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">ECOLOGY AND EVOLUTION</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof TP Hughes; Dr KR Anthony; Dr AH Baird; Prof DR Bellwood; Dr SR Connolly; Dr SG Dove; Dr M Fine; Prof C Folke; Dr MK Gagan; Prof O Hoegh-Guldberg; Dr MS Pratchett; Dr GP Jones; Prof RH Karlson; Prof MJ Kingsford; Dr JM Lough; Dr MI McCormick; Prof MT McCulloch; Dr M Meekan; Dr DJ Miller; Dr PL Munday; Dr JM Pandolfi; Dr S Planes; A/Prof GR Russ; Prof R Steneck; Dr RH Bradbury; Dr MJ van Oppen; Dr LJ McCook; A/Prof BL Willis; Prof D Yellowlees; Dr C Pelejero
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 21,800,000.00
Application Year: 2004
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Our vision is to apply enabling technologies to capture the national benefit arising from research excellence. The Centre has enormous capacity to provide economic, cultural, environmental and social benefits for Australia. The coral reefs of Australia, particularly the Great Barrier Reef, Ningaloo Reef, and Lord Howe Island World Heritage Area are Australian national icons, of great economic, social, and aesthetic value to this country. In collaboration with our Partners, we will be the premier providers of the scientific expertise that underpins the management of Australian reefs, which is vital for the sustainable use of biodiversity goods and services (e.g. by the tourist industry, fisheries, and recreational users).

</description>
      <description type="brief">The primary goal of this Centre of Excellence is to develop research programs of international significance (through the establishment of new collaborative teams of Australia's leading coral reef researchers) that transcend traditional disciplinary, institutional and geographic boundaries. Our aim is to add focus, scale and scope to build an enduring program of innovative research development, leading to world leadership in coral reef science. A key outcome of the Centre will be to actively transfer scientific knowledge (through its governance structure) to industry partners and end-users, to increase their capacity and effectiveness and provide tangible benefits to all Australians.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989294</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989294</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989294</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Koorie archiving: Community and records working together</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-507067</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">CULTURAL STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms S Faulkhead; Prof LW Russell; Prof SM McKemmish
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 190,000.00
Application Year: 2008
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">The integration, preservation and accessibility of all archival sources, forms and media of Koorie knowledge are vital to processes of recovery for those affected by past government policies and to national reconciliation. Working in partnership with the Gunditjmara community of the Victorian Western District and the Koorie Heritage Trust, the Project will assist Koorie and other Indigenous communities to access and control information about them and their culture, and to build sustainable community archives. This will help in establishing identity, reconnecting families, pursuing land claims, intergenerational healing, preserving culture, and redress. The Project will place Australia at the forefront of Indigenous archiving research.</description>
      <description type="brief">The Bringing Them Home Report stressed the right of Indigenous people to manage their knowledge in all forms, recognising access to archives and community control of historical documentation as vital components of reconciliation. However there are no robust frameworks, processes and protocols for managing community-based Koorie archives. The Project will address this gap. Using a Koorie community case study and participatory research model, it will map all archival sources, forms and media of community knowledge and explore the community's desired interaction with its archive. Project outcomes will support sustainable community-based Koorie archives, and contribute to more culturally sensitive archiving principles and practices generally.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0238938</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0238938</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0238938</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Diversity and Discipline: The Impact of Punishment on Indigenous Students' Attitudes Toward Schooling</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-574210</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">OTHER EDUCATION</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr V Sanderson Ms P Thomson
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 16,670.00
Application Year: 2001
First Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">The research will focus on punishment as an organising principle of schools and from empirical research, will construct a discourse within which discipline as power can be discussed. The research offers a new approach to investigations on the disciplinary practices of schools and challenges the concept of regimes of punishment as a necessary adjunct to learning. At the same time, it develops an Indigenous methodology which calls on participants as co-researchers to tell their stories as a critical aspect of grounded research</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882982</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882982</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882982</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Building and supporting community led partnership initiatives to respond to Indigenous family violence in Victoria</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593909</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">PUBLIC HEALTH AND HEALTH SERVICES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr KA Cripps; Prof IP Anderson; Prof ML Langton; Dr MM Walter; A/Prof MJ Rose
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 200,000.00
Application Year: 2007
First Year: 2008
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This project contributes to the evidence base of responses to Indigenous family violence by detailing models of practice in Victoria.  It will focus on how partnerships between Indigenous and mainstream responses can be built and sustained.  The critical analysis of these models of practice and partnerships will also have implications for future policy and funding directions.  The research will be most beneficial within the local family violence sector.  The research methodology facilitates a process of information brokerage and critical reflection within and between Indigenous and mainstream family violence interventions that may influence ongoing community and organisational practices.</description>
      <description type="brief">The research will examine Indigenous and mainstream models of practice that respond to Indigenous family violence and how these models build and nurture partnerships for future sustainability. Through forums and publications, the research will increase knowledge about family violence, in turn leading to the improved health and wellbeing of Indigenous communities. The research will also have direct relevance and implications for future policy and funding directions. The study will be significant: in process (led by an Indigenous researcher and supported by key Indigenous academics); in methodology (levels of ethical consultation and participation of Indigenous communities); and in outcomes.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100113</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100113</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100113</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Wingara Mangami (to follow the dream of understanding): Seeding innovative intervention success to challenge and pracism for Inyouth</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-485355</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">PSYCHOLOGY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr Gawaian H Bodkin-Andrews; Prof Rhonda G Craven
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 348,000.00
Application Year: 2009
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Intervention to combat racism towards Indigenous youth is vital given the pervasiveness and long-term consequences for academic failure, mental health costs and anti-social behaviour. Consistent with the priority of promoting andmaintaining good health and well-being, the study offers important educational and socio-economic benefits by enriching the psychosocial adjustment and life potential of Indigenous Australians. Effective intervention to address racism will enhance pro-social behaviours, self-concept, mental health, and school engagement of Indigenous secondary students and build capacity of non-Indigenous students to address racism and foster safer schools that contribute to individual, local community, and national well-being.</description>
      <description type="brief">Racism towards Indigenous youth is a pervasive problem with long-term adverse psychosocial consequences for Australia. Research has demonstrated that racism impacts upon the mental health, life potential and educational outcomes of Indigenous Australians. Grounded on cutting-edge interdisciplinary theory and research, and as a logical and necessary progression of my successful ARC funded development of research-derived intervention strategies I will: explicate psychosocial determinants/consequences of racism; implement an innovative new intervention and test its impact on pro-social behaviours, mental health, wellbeing and academic functioning of Indigenous secondary students using a powerful longitudinal design and multi-method analyses.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0562063</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0562063</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0562063</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence in Structural and Functional Microbial Genomics</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-507067</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">MICROBIOLOGY</subject>
      <description type="Community Benefit">The research falls under the National Research Priority Frontier Technologies for Building and Transforming Australian Industries, with the priority goal of frontier technologies.  The research  has commercial applications, such as the development of novel antimicrobials and vaccines, with potentially enormous impact in the biotechnology area of biomedical health and the primary industries. In addition, the project will use state-of-the-art technology, including use of synchrotron radiation at the Monash-based Australian Synchrotron facility from 2007.</description>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof B Adler; Prof RL Coppel; Prof JK Davies; A/Prof RJ Devenish; Prof P Nagley; Prof JI Rood; Dr J Rossjohn; Prof IA Smith; Dr JC Whisstock
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 15,250,000.00
Application Year: 2004
</description>
      <description type="brief">Australian Primary Industry will benefit from a team of experts in microbial genetics, bioinformatics and protein structure and function undertaking integrated studies on microbial genomics that are focused on fundamental biological processes and host/pathogen interactions. Whole genome expression and protein profiling will be used to characterise genes whose expression is altered in the infected host and to analyse genes involved in the control of key cellular processes. The Centre will also determine the shapes of key molecules and their interactions. Practical outcomes will include new veterinary vaccines and the identification of novel antimicrobial targets.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208033</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208033</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208033</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Probing JNK MAPK function with peptide inhibitors</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-464686</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">BIOCHEMISTRY AND CELL BIOLOGY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr MA Bogoyevitch Dr PM Watt
Scheme: Discovery Projects
Funding: $AUD 141,000.00
Application Year: 2001
First Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">It has generally been accepted that the JNK MAPK family of protein kinases is rapidly and potently activated following the exposure of mammalian cells to stresses and cytokines. However, their biological role has remained controversial. We believe that this problem reflects the lack of a generally applicable and specific JNK MAPK inhibitor. In this project we continue our characterisation of a small peptide inhibitor developed in our laboratories. We aim to determine its mechanism of inhibition, the specificity of interaction, and to evolve more effective inhibitors. With these new inhibitors, we can effectively address the biological roles of these kinases.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348249</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348249</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348249</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre for Complex Systems (ACCS)</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-460867</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE AND SIGNAL AND IMAGE PROCESSING</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof PA LindsayProf DG GreenProf IJ HayesProf GI WebbDr HA AbbassProf DA AbramsonDr P AdamsProf TR BossomaierProf K BurrageProf RG DromeyProf J FosterProf SM KaplanProf GJ McLachlanProf BA PailthorpeProf PM SandersonProf HW SchmidtA/Prof KA Smith
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 5,208,295.00
Application Year: 2002
First Year: 2003
</description>
      <description type="brief">The Australian Centre for Complex Systems brings together leading researchers from several disciplines and institutions to conduct research on questions fundamental to understanding and managing complex systems. Its core research program, based on the theme of computation in and by networks of agents, has two interwoven strands. The science strand addresses questions about emergent properties, natural computation, and nonlinear dynamics. The engineering strand addresses issues about methodology, modelling toolkits, and management and control. Practical applications are advanced via collaborative projects that address key issues in biology, environment, and socio-economics.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0560757</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0560757</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0560757</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Identification and Characterisation of Genes involved in the Copper Regulation of the Human Alzheimer's Disease Amyloid-Beta Precursor Protein (APP) Gene</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593909</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">GENETICS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr SA Bellingham; A/Prof J Camakaris; Prof DK Lahiri; Dr R Cappai; Prof CL Masters
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 160,896.00
Application Year: 2004
First Year: 2005
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Alzheimer's disease (AD) is the most common form of dementia in the ageing population. This research project aims to identify and characterise new genes involved in the copper regulation of the Alzheimer's disease gene.  This may lead to the development of novel therapeutic targets and clinical intervention strategies as well as early diagnostic procedures in preventative healthcare for the treatment of AD. The benefits would affect the international community as a whole, potentially minimising the socio-economic costs arising from the predicted world-wide increase in AD in the ageing population.</description>
      <description type="brief">Alzheimer's disease (AD) is the most common neurodegenerative disorder in the ageing population. The main causative factor of AD, is the cleavage of the amyloid-beta precursor protein (APP), resulting in excessive deposition of toxic amyloid-beta peptide in AD brains. Elucidating mechanisms of regulation of the APP gene is important in the development and control of AD pathogenesis. This project aims to gain a comprehensive understanding of the novel copper regulation of the human APP gene. Identification and characterisation of new regulatory genes in the copper regulation of the APP gene may lead to the development of novel therapeutic targets and clinical intervention strategies in preventative healthcare for treatment of AD.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989770</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989770</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989770</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Solid Kids Solid Schools: conceptualising bullying in an Aboriginal context as reported by the Yamaji community</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-589763</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">PUBLIC HEALTH AND HEALTH SERVICES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms J Coffin; Prof B Down; Prof DS Cross
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 80,000.00
Application Year: 2008
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This project holds significant national benefit as the correlations between health and education outcomes are well evidenced as is the unacceptable inequity in education outcomes for Indigenous and non-Indigenous children.  It seeks to improve school attendance, retention and academic achievements, as well as quality of school experience for Aboriginal children</description>
      <description type="brief">This innovative project will conceptualise bullying within the context of the WA Yamaji community and develop and implement an Aboriginal specific school and community-based bullying prevention and reduction program.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348205</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348205</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348205</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre for the Kangaroo Genome</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-595489</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">GENETICS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr R ToderProf JA GravesProf MB RenfreeProf DW CooperProf TP SpeedProf JS Mattick
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Application Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">In this Australian-led Kangaroo Genome Project, we will map and characterize the tammar wallaby genome at the molecular level. Marsupial genomes are uniquely valuable because they provide comparisons that reveal new human genes, regulatory sequences and marsupial-specific genes. These will deliver new products and information useful for medicine, industry, agriculture and conservation. We will construct integrated genetic and physical maps of the genome, clone the whole genome as large inserts in BAC vectors, and build a ?golden path? with minimal overlap. We will construct libraries of expressed genes from tammar tissues and array them for use in analysing gene expression.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/AR04/00252</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:58Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/AR04/00252</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/AR04/00252</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Anglo-Australian Observatory Research Fellowship</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-474309</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local"/>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: n.a.
Scheme: AAO
Funding: $AUD 159,218.00
Application Year: continuing
</description>
      <description type="brief">The Anglo-Australian Observatory Fellowship is managed by the Anglo-Australian Telescope Board through the Anglo-Australian Observatory (AAO) and co-funded on a 50/50 basis by the ARC and the UK Particle Physics and Astronomy Research Council (PPARC). Each year one Fellowship is awarded alternately to Australian and British early career researchers to undertake postdoctoral work at the Anglo-Australian Observatory. The period of tenure of the Fellowship is two years with provision of an extension of up to 12 months in exceptional circumstances.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0560542</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0560542</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0560542</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">TOWARD ANANGU PEDAGOGICAL APPROACHES TO TRANSMISSION OF KNOWLEDGE AND PARALLEL EDUCATIONAL PARADIGMS: Song-cycle from senior women of the Antikirinya/Yankuntjatjara community.</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593299</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">EDUCATION STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms S Tur; Dr C Nicholls; A/Prof TA Bunda
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 60,720.00
Application Year: 2004
First Year: 2005
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">The need for understanding Anangu pedagogical approaches to transmission of knowledges is toward an Australian priority to develop schooling that upholds Indigenous interests. The structure of the project calls for a comprehensive literature review and data collection via interviews around Anangu Song-Cycle.  While others researchers have touched upon Song-Cycles, in depth-analysis of the specific context of Anangu Song-Cycles are largely unexamined. To date there have been no analysis conducted by Anangu academics themselves. The implementation of the research findings will have implications for Anangu communities in the changing way schools construct curricula and knowledge transmission for Anangu.</description>
      <description type="brief">This project aims to critically examine theories about song-cycle from senior Antikirinya/Yankuntjatjara women. It does so by asking what methods of transmission and their knowledges are used in these song-cycle traditions. The research is informed by analysis of key texts on Indigenous song-cycles and will document Elders voices in relation to teaching method and its contemporary relevance. The significance of this research is twofold. The candidate is the first Antikirinya/Yankuntjatjara women to research about song-cycle that shifts analysis from Ethnomusicology to Education. Outcomes include completion of PhD canditure and mapping concepts of song-cycle traditions to developing categories for theoretical analysis.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0560958</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0560958</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0560958</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Spiritual Journeying and Cross- culturalism: The Art of Tim Johnson</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593909</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">OTHER ARTS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr D Leslie; Dr CR Marshall
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 166,743.00
Application Year: 2004
First Year: 2005
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This project will benefit the Australian community through new research on Tim Johnson , one of Australia's outstanding contemporary artists. Its exploration of the spiritual nature and the cross-cultural aspects of his work, especially in relation to Aboriginal Art, will provide a strong basis for further comparative research on the history of the relationship between art and spirituality in contemporary Australian art.  The resulting book and possible exhibition on this artist will make the fruits of this research widely known in the community.</description>
      <description type="brief">This project will explore the work of the Australian artist Tim Johnson, tracing his creative development, sources and the conceptual framework of his art. In particular it will analyse a select body of his art with reference to cross-culturalism, and art as a spiritual journey. Today, Johnson is primarily inspired by Buddhism but he has also investigated other non-western spiritual traditions, particularly Aboriginal art and collaborated with both Aboriginal and Asian artists. This project will advance our understanding of cross-culturalism and spirituality in the visual arts. Its findings will be communicated in a book and conference papers and possibly an exhibition</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989059</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989059</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989059</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Attention Deficit Hyper Activity Disorder: A critical analysis elucidating constructs that influence parental acceptance/rejection of diagnosis and response</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-485355</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">EDUCATION STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr AW Dillon; Prof RG Craven; Dr AS Yeung; Prof I Wilson
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 90,000.00
Application Year: 2008
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Part of the controversy surrounding ADHD is the increasing use of stimulant medication to deal with children who have been given a diagnosis of ADHD. Given the absence of scientific evidence that demonstrates an underlying causal physical pathology for ADHD, many claim that medication is inappropriate, with some suggesting that it is harmful. This research seeks to explicate parents' perceptions of ADHD &amp; the impact of psycho-social constructs on parents' decisions to accept/reject a diagnosis &amp; respond. This research offers important educational &amp; social benefits. The outcomes of this research have the potential to 'break the cycle' of increasing medication; build parents' capacity to respond; &amp; contribute to a healthy start to life.</description>
      <description type="brief">Increasingly Australian children are being medicated for ADHD. ADHD as a medical explanation for the inattentive &amp;/or hyperactive behaviour of some children is a very contentious issue. Some parents &amp; professionals believe ADHD to be a proven medical disorder, others vehemently doubt its validity. There is a paucity of research explicating parents' decision-making &amp; responses. This research seeks to capitalize on cutting-edge interdisciplinary theory &amp; research &amp; an innovative multi-method design to elucidate parents' perceptions of ADHD &amp; the impact of psycho-social constructs on parents' decisions to accept/reject a diagnosis &amp; respond. This will result in building the capacity of parents &amp; contribute to a healthy start to life.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775799</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775799</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775799</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">How young (2-4 years) Indigenous learners come to know and not know early mathematical language and processes</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536697</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">CURRICULUM STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mrs GE Sarra; Dr AR Baturo
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 99,000.00
Application Year: 2006
First Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">The project focuses on strengthening Australia's social and economic fabric by developing new knowledge about effective ways to prepare young Australian Indigenous children for mathematics success in school. Low Indigenous mathematics performance is a national shame - many school leavers have limited employment and life chances. A theory that explains 2-4 years old Indigenous students' cognitive, affective and sociocultural development of the necessary number language and processes to ensure school entry with similar number knowledge and practices to same age non-Indigenous students has the potential to reduce unemployment and the reliance on welfare that has led to many of the social and health problems of Indigenous communities.</description>
      <description type="brief">Australian Indigenous students' mathematics performance continues to be below that of non-Indigenous students. This occurs from the early years of school, due largely to knowledge, affect and social differences on entry to formal schooling. This project aims to identify and explain the ways that young Australian Indigenous students (age 2-4 years) know and not know, learn and not learn early number language and processes (particularly attribute language, sorting, 1-1 correspondence, counting) in the prior-to-school environments of home and early child care or play group settings. This will inform professionals on the necessary prior-to-school activities to prepare Indigenous students for success in mathematics at Kindergarten and school.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0240648</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0240648</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0240648</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">My Island Home - Construction of cultural identity for Torres Strait Islanders who migrated to the mainland post World War Two.</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-642603</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">CULTURAL STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms F Watkin Dr SC McGinty
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 24,522.00
Application Year: 2001
First Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">The aims of the research are to examine 1) the construction of cultural identity for Torres Strait Islanders who migrated to Cairns during 1946 to 1955 and 2) to identify issues in relation to the construction and maintenance of cultural identity; the Islander's 'integration' into Australian society; and the transitional processes they negotiated in establishing new communities away from the Torres Strait. This project is significant as it is one of the very few research projects conducted by a Torres Strait Islander on this issue, and its outcome will be a new perspective on the migration and culture of Torres Strait Islander people.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0240782</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0240782</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0240782</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">A Historical Study of Indigenous Higher Education Centres in Australia</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-595489</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">OTHER STUDIES IN HUMAN SOCIETY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms FC Peters-Little Dr J Schwab Prof JC Altman
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 20,000.00
Application Year: 2001
First Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">Indigenous education centres have evolved and emerged across Australian universities for over thirty years, yet there has never been an independent chronological study of their historical development at the national level. This research documents the visions of those people who instigated the early development of Indigenous education centres in higher education, recording how their early development influenced or was influenced by Indigenous communities and individuals, or by government and university policies. From their humble beginnings right through to their present day expansion and diversity, the project aims to become an important contribution towards Aboriginal history and Australian higher education studies.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561574</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561574</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561574</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence - Design in Light Metals</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-507067</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">MATERIALS ENGINEERING</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof BC Muddle; Prof PD Hodgson; Prof G Schaffer; A/Prof M Ferry; A/Prof SP Ringer; A/Prof K Xia; Dr J Nie; Dr CH Davies; Dr CR Hutchinson; Dr MR Barnett; A/Prof AK Dahle; A/Prof CH Caceres; A/Prof MJ Hoffman; Prof GL Dunlop; Dr M Couper; Em/Prof JD Embury; Prof MH Loretto OBE; Prof FJ Humphreys; Prof LE Arnberg; Prof YS Estrin; Dr HL Fraser; Prof Y Brechet
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 22,550,000.00
Application Year: 2004
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Under the national Light Metals Action Agenda, Australia recognizes a strategic interest in the production, processing and applications of the light metals, and a growth in global markets for light metals technology. Light metals research is a designated national priority, and this Centre will provide the national focus in strategic fundamental research, the critical level of investment and the level of innovation necessary to achieve competitive advantage from an outstanding research base. As a major contributor to a strategic network of national research capabilities, it will underpin substantial developments in the light metals industry nationally and globally, and extend linkages with major research centres internationally.</description>
      <description type="brief">The Centre will adopt a systematic process of 'virtual materials selection' to assess modifications to the property profiles of light metals systems that will maximize the competitiveness of light alloys and new light metal hybrid materials based on aluminium, magnesium and titanium. Using a novel 'design-directed' approach to fundamental research, it will address strategic design targets through innovations in structural design at the nanoscale and advances in processing, to enhance the properties of existing alloys economically. It will also embrace innovation in design of light metal systems to create novel hybrid and surface-modified materials that expand the range of properties available and thus the applications for light metals.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0561141</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0561141</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0561141</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">New Solutions For Maximising Secondary Indigenous Students? Full Potential: Identifying Causal Constructs That Enhance Indigenous Students' Aspirations and Educational Outcomes</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-485355</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">EDUCATION STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr GH Bodkin Andrews; A/Prof RG Craven
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 37,942.00
Application Year: 2004
First Year: 2005
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">The proposed research offers important educational and social benefits for righting the disadvantaged status of Indigenous Australians within the secondary education system. Identifying specific psychological constructs that act as potent keys directly impacting on Indigenous students educational aspirations will eventually assist Indigenous students in reaching their full potential. In identifying these causal constructs, potent new interventions can then be created to enhance Indigenous schooling, create a stronger capital base in Aboriginal communities, and ensure a stronger Indigenous Australian representative population who will aid in shaping a better future for Australia.</description>
      <description type="brief">Research has demonstrated that Indigenous students set lower educational aspirations than non-Indigenous students within secondary school. With a string of studies highlighting the need for accurate intervention strategies encompassing skill development and psychological processing, it?s the purpose of this research to offer a comprehensive longitudinal study to clarify the effect various psychological determinants have on attaining desirable aspirations and educational outcomes for Indigenous students. It is hoped a potent practical foundation will be formed to help contribute to new interventions aimed at reversing the disadvantaged status of Indigenous students within the education system.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882986</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882986</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882986</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">The impact of climate change on the resilience of Australian marine systems: linking climate and ecosystem models</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-460867</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">FISHERIES SCIENCES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms CM Hunter; Dr AJ Richardson; Dr EA Fulton; Prof HP Possingham
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 160,000.00
Application Year: 2007
First Year: 2008
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This project will underpin Australia's long-term commitment to maintain environmental biodiversity and sustainability in the face of climate change. We will describe the consequences of climate change on marine processes, harvested resources and ecosystem functioning by identifying vulnerable species and habitats. We will provide management advice on balancing ecosystem integrity, economic efficiency, and ecosystem resilience under climate change. This information is of immediate use by a range of Australian stakeholders including national, state and local government agencies. The project will put Australian scientists at the forefront of research focused on the adaptation of marine ecosystems to climate impacts.</description>
      <description type="brief">Australia is particularly vulnerable to climate change because of our unique marine biodiversity and the significant economic wealth marine systems generate. Currently, the science needed to manage biological impacts of climate change lags far behind our knowledge of physical oceanic changes. We will develop a modelling approach linking global climate and ecosystem models for predicting climate change impacts on marine life using the leading marine ecosystem model in the region. This will enable evaluation of management strategies that can be applied to protect biodiversity, increase resilience of marine ecosystems, and provide sustained economic benefit for Australia under climate change.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100014</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100014</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100014</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">'To wake them up again': Digital futures for the international diaspora of early ethnographic collections from Arnhem Land</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593941</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">CULTURAL STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr Joseph N Gumbula
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 366,000.00
Application Year: 2009
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Informed by the Indigenous inheritors of Arnhem Land's endangered languages and traditions, this project will produce findings of world-heritage significance that will inform the importance of early ethnographic collections held in museums worldwide to well-being and cultural survival in our local communities. There is enormous local interest in our region's recorded history. In recent years, the return of digitised materials from significant ethnographic collections has helped to stimulate the on-going maintenance of our cultures markedly. The sense of history that they bring is proving invaluable in maintaining well-being and community amid the hardships of local life, and in particular, in stimulating youth engagement with tradition.</description>
      <description type="brief">Drawing on my experience as a Yolngu elder with research expertise in Curatorial Studies, this project will assess historical materials from Arnhem Land held by museums in Europe, the USA and Australia. Dating from 1924, these materials collected by Wilkins, Webb, Warner, Elkin and Berndt include the oldest ethnographic records of Yolngu culture in Arnhem Land. My explorations of these materials will refer to the continuing traditional frameworks that guide community life in Arnhem Land. I will also evaluate the impact of international relations and digital technologies in addressing needs for sustained remote Indigenous community access to such materials, and bring the voices of contemporary elders from Arnhem Land to bear on these issues.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775835</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775835</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775835</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">A study to determine the relevance to Australian Indigenous lands of allotment in the United States of America</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-502828</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">LAW</subject>
      <description type="brief">The project will contribute to the debate over the privatisation of Indigenous lands with a comparative analysis of the fragmentation of Native American lands. The General Allotment Act of 1887 facilitated the fragmentation of Native American Reservations with the aim of encouraging individual property rights. It resulted in the loss of Native American lands and was abandoned in the earlier part of the twentieth century. The researcher will draw upon American case law and critical analysis of the allotment system. The research will form the basis of academic journal articles and conference papers.</description>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms NL Watson; Prof Dr LY Behrendt
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 10,000.00
Application Year: 2006
First Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">The research will address the national research priority of promoting and maintaining good health. In particular, it will address the goal of strengthening Australia's social and economic fabric by assisting Indigenous communities to make informed decisions about the future use of their lands.  </description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775808</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775808</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775808</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Preventative health interventions for Indigenous children less than six years of age.</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593909</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">PUBLIC HEALTH AND HEALTH SERVICES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms K Adams; Dr K Rowley; Prof IP Anderson
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 165,240.00
Application Year: 2006
First Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">It is well established that poor early childhood health has affects into adult life, for example, the relationship between child growth and development and likelihood of developing adult chronic disease. Some information is available about Victorian Indigenous children's health status; however little is known about effectiveness of preventative health interventions. This research proposes to work with Aboriginal community controlled services to develop preventative interventions and measure consequent changes to child health outcomes. This will be achieved through building an initial evidence base from available data and service audits. This information will be used to develop interventions and identify measurable variables.</description>
      <description type="brief">Aim Develop preventative health interventions for Victorian Indigenous children &lt; six years of age and measure change. Significance Victorian Indigenous children have poorer health outcomes compared to non-Indigenous. despite this few studies of children's health have been conducted, particularly of health improvements. Studies have shown nutrition, housing, infection, financial security, family stress, tobacco smoke and access to health and early childhood services as impacting on Victorian Indigenous children's health. This study proposes to work with Aboriginal community controlled services to develop interventions and measure changes from these. Outcomes Inform policy and practice in regard to improving health of Koorie children.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348155</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:58Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348155</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348155</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence for Advanced Silicon Photovoltaics and Photonics</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593921</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">ELECTRICAL AND ELECTRONIC ENGINEERING</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof SR WenhamProf MA GreenDr O BreitensteinProf A PolmanAdj/Prof PA BasoreA/Prof AG AberleA/Prof CB HonsbergA/Prof J ZhaoDr KR CatchpoleDr PR CampbellDr G ConibeerDr RP CorkishDr JE CotterDr X DaiDr T PuzzerDr AB SproulDr T TrupkeDr A Wang
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 19,375,000.00
Application Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">Silicon photovoltaics (Si PV) is a priority area within the Photon Science and Technology category. Multiple studies have identified PV solar electricity as the most promising option for a sustainable energy future, with Australia already at the forefront internationally in Si PV. The applicants recently have shown that insights from PV also may provide the key to the successful development of active Si photonic devices for integration into microelectronics. The Centre?s aims and expected outcomes are to strengthen this technological lead in Si PV while pioneering the development of active Si photonic devices for microelectronic integration, with economic, cultural and social benefits.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0348109</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0348109</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0348109</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Indigenous Research Methodologies: Frameworks toward Indigenous Intellectual Sovereignty and the Decolonisation of Research</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593299</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">OTHER STUDIES IN HUMAN SOCIETY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr L Rigney Prof GR Worby Dr C Nicholls
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 74,332.00
Application Year: 2002
First Year: 2003
</description>
      <description type="brief">This project aims to critically examine theories and methods of research enquiry emerging from contemporary Indigenous Australian research scholarship. It does so by asking ?what is Indigenous about Indigenous research? and ?can there be a distinctive Indigenous Australian perspective on epistemology, methodology and philosophy of research?? The research will be informed by analysis of key text/ discourses on Indigenous research methodologies by Indigenous scholars engaged in transformative praxis. Outcomes include the completion of a PhD candidature, mapping concepts and theories of Indigenous Research Methodologies, developing an Indigenous intellectual framework to assist Indigenous scholars to negotiate knowledge production and research methodologies.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348243</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348243</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348243</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre for Functional Nanomaterials</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-460867</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">CIVIL ENGINEERING</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof GM Lu; Prof JW White; A/Prof R Amal; Prof DL Trimm; Prof SC Smith; Prof Dr AB YuDr Y ChenProf J DrennanProf MA WilsonDr IR GentleA/Prof MP BrungsProf M TrauDr JC Diniz da CostaDr DJ MartinDr A HillProf AW MauDr B RaguseDr CJ HawkerProf KL Wooley
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 12,463,180.00
Application Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">The Centre will consist of leading researchers from four Australian universities, four CSIRO divisions, and two US research centres. The vision is to position Australia as a world leader in nanomaterials science and technology. The Centre will involve nanoscale science for building functional nanostructures of materials at the molecular level. It aims to develop new methods and techniques for self-assembling and characterizing nanomaterials with tailorable properties. The outcomes will include leading-edge science, the development of human capital, and intellectual property in new materials and products for applications in clean energy, environmental, and health care industries.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0668361</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0668361</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0668361</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Reading as a cultural and historical practice</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-597924</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">CULTURAL STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr B Collins-Gearing
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 20,000.00
Application Year: 2005
First Year: 2006
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">A better understanding and use of reading as an academic tool for Indigenous and non-Indigenous students and educators will be a result of the research. It will provide a new understanding of how reading skills can be used by Indigenous students to comprehend academic information and how academics can approach reading without excluding Indigenous knowledges.</description>
      <description type="brief">The project will investigate how reading is both a colonising and a decolonising act. The focus is on how Indigenous students, as readers of academic texts, can be either empowered or disempowered through the act of reading. By examining how reading, in academic contexts, has privileged non-Indigenous Australians, this project will reveal how Indigenous Australians have engaged reading for Indigenous purposes.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561595</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561595</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561595</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence in Ore Deposits</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-460913</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">GEOLOGY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof RR Large; A/Prof JB Gemmell; Prof AJ Crawford; Prof J McPhie; Prof SF Cox; Dr DR Cooke; Prof Dr G Garven; Dr JE Reid; Prof JC Macnae; Dr PK Fullagar; Dr R Tosdal; Prof MW Hitzman; Dr SG Walters; Prof Dr J Franzidis; Prof TJ Napier-Munn; Dr LV Danyushevsky; A/Prof JM Hergt; Dr CG Ryan; Dr D Giles; Dr V Kamenetsky; Dr AC Harris; Dr SW Bull; Dr GJ Davidson; A/Prof JW Hedenquist; Dr PJ McGoldrick; Dr C Deyell; Dr MJ Roach; Dr RF Berry; Dr K Zaw
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 24,450,000.00
Application Year: 2004
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Australia's minerals industry faces a two-fold challenge - to find new ore deposits and to mine them with maximum efficiency and minimal environmental impact. Those challenges demand a new generation of focussed ore deposit research, tailored specifically for the Australian context. The Centre of Excellence in Ore Deposits will provide the foundation of fundamental research required by a successful, efficient and sustainable Australian minerals industry. The Centre will also play a leading role in the undergraduate and postgraduate training of future geoscientists. The concentration of internationally recognised researchers in the Centre will ensure it maintains its premier position in the international ore deposit research arena.</description>
      <description type="brief">The Centre of Excellence in Ore Deposits will encompass an innovative program of multidisciplinary research in ore deposit location, formation, discovery and recovery. Innovative fundamental research on where ore deposits occur, how they form and their deep earth signatures, will give our minerals industry a new scientific framework in which to search for ore. The existing ARC Special Research Centre for Ore Deposit Research has played a pivotal role in Australia's current leadership in mineral exploration-related research. The new Centre of Excellence will build on this success by increasing collaboration and expanding into new research areas critical to the growth of Australia's minerals industry.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0347284</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0347284</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0347284</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">The Aboriginal Fight for Liberty and Freedom - The hidden history of African-American influence on the 1920s rise of Aboriginal political activism.</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-565275</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">HISTORICAL STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr J Maynard Prof J Ramsland
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 80,000.00
Application Year: 2002
First Year: 2003
</description>
      <description type="brief">This project will explore the significant African-American influences on the rise of the 1920s Aboriginal political movement. Previously undisclosed material revealed over the past two years has necessitated a re-evaluation of early Australian Aboriginal political history. Why was the history of the rise of early Aboriginal political activism missing for some five decades? Why were significant relationships with high profile African-American identities obscured and erased from memories? The research outcomes from this archival study will make a contribution to the contemporary issues surrounding reconciliation and the current volatile historical debate over Aboriginal history. This project holds significant international racial historical importance.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208012</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208012</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208012</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">A new approach to the generation of long-lived charge-separated states in rigid Donor-Bridge-Acceptor systems</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593921</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">ORGANIC CHEMISTRY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof MN Paddon-Row
Scheme: Discovery Projects
Funding: $AUD 520,000.00
Application Year: 2001
First Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">Electron transfer and energy transfer are ubiquitous in nature and they provide the key to the design of energy transducing materials. Considerable effort is being expended into studying light-induced electron transfer which leads to the formation of a charge-separated state or molecular "battery". To be useful, these batteries should have lifetimes at least in the microsecond domain and this is not easily achieved in practice. This project will explore a new, elegant, and promising approach to the efficient generation of very long-lived charge-separated states in rigid systems, which is based on triplet sensitisation.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100145</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100145</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100145</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Through travellers' eyes: Foreign observations of Aboriginal people and British colonisation, 1800-1850</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-595489</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">HISTORICAL STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr Shino A Konishi; Prof Ann Curthoys; Prof Stephen R Garton; Prof Ann M McGrath
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 155,000.00
Application Year: 2009
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This project will enhance our historical understanding of a crucial stage in the colonisation of Aboriginal people. It will uncover a new corpus of historical sources which has not been subject to sustained study, and bring to light instances of nineteenth-century Aboriginal agency. Most importantly, it will highlight nineteenth-century discourses on the colonial treatment of indigenous people, and therefore enable a deeper knowledge of Indigenous Australian history to inform public debates on matters of policy, identity, and culture.</description>
      <description type="brief">This project critically examines encounters between travellers and Aboriginal people throughout Australia in the first half of the nineteenth century. It examines how these encounters affected the Western travellers' engagement with Victorian anthropological thought and provoked criticism of British imperialism. Aboriginal history will benefit from a more complex picture of nineteenth-century ideas about Aborigines. I will highlight diverse critiques of settler-colonialism which were not limited to Christian or humanitarian concerns.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0240879</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0240879</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0240879</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">A Case Study Analysis of Indigenous Australian Entrepreneurs Exploring the Retention of Indigenous Values</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-460913</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">BUSINESS AND MANAGEMENT</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr D Foley
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 24,050.00
Application Year: 2001
First Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">The research project explores the possible changes or loss of cultural values on the Indigenous Australian Entrepreneurs from their involvement in founding and managing their own business. Does the Indigenous entrepreneur become in effect culturally non-indigenous whilst engaged in entrepreneurial activity? or, are the individuals cultural values maintained, transformed, subdued in some other context? These are the questions that this proposed research hopes to answer. The study is concerned with the connection between Anglo-European business values and general Indigenous cultural values. Little research has been published on Indigenous entrepreneurship; this project will fill a void in current literature in this area.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0668285</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0668285</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0668285</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Testing Ground: Investigating Indigenous Knowledge Programs and Indigenous Research Methodologies in Higher Education.</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-460867</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">CURRICULUM STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr N Sheehan; Em/Prof JS Western
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 48,570.00
Application Year: 2005
First Year: 2006
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This project will contribute to Australian social cohesion through the non-divisive Indigenous Knowledge approach to the teaching of Indigenous issues. Indigenous Knowledge Research is a new methodological development that will afford research in many cross-cultural contexts including those where literacy and numeracy skills are low. This research methodology has national and community significance because it fosters social cohesion in investigating problematic contexts through methods that bridge across groups and build community capacities to engage, identify and implement self-owned solutions. This research will facilitate the instigation of informational gathering structures in the most marginalized sectors of the Australian community.</description>
      <description type="brief">Indigenous Knowledge (IK) is a relational understanding that values interconnectedness. This research project aims to investigate early career teachers perceptions of the value, relevance and significance of Indigenous Knowledge programs in their teaching practice and to further the development and test the effectiveness, veracity and validity of Indigenous Research Methodologies (IKR). Teacher experiences as they engage IK approaches in their classroom practice will be investigated through an IKR model which mutualises inquiry, problem mediation and participant support. A deeper objective of the project is to create templates for translating research findings across IKR and normative Social Science methodologies...</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0454216</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0454216</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0454216</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Issues of Identity, Place and Belonging in Recent Works of Australian Autobiography</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-460832</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">CULTURAL STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms SJ Kurtzer; Prof Dr KL Schaffer; A/Prof ME Allen
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 33,512.00
Application Year: 2003
First Year: 2004
</description>
      <description type="brief">This project addresses issues of identity, place and belonging in Australia specifically in recent autobiographical works by Australian writers. It examines and compares selected life narratives of Indigenous and non-Indigenous writers in order to explore how these texts differently configure identity as well as how these understandings have been interpreted by Indigenous and non-Indigenous critics and readers. The project will map the changes within public debates including the significant social, political and cultural consequences for all involved. A number of conference papers and published articles will contribute to the debates from an Indigenous perspective, extending critical perspectives within Australian cultural domains.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989086</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989086</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989086</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Evaluation of an Instrument to Assess the Needs of Indigenous Patients with Cancer</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-597924</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">PUBLIC HEALTH AND HEALTH SERVICES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms G Garvey; Dr VL Beesley; Dr PC Valery; Dr M Janda; Dr PK O'Rourke; Prof AC Green
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 185,000.00
Application Year: 2008
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">There is an urgent need to address the differentials in health outcomes for Indigenous populations through a variety of programs addressing access to cancer care. An important part of any health program is measurement of health outcomes. This proposed research will develop and evaluate culturally sensitive needs assessment tools to ensure that the future of service provision is targeted to meet the priority needs of Indigenous cancer patients. Armed with an appropriate understanding of Indigenous peoples needs and how to assess these, care provision will be able to improve and maintain good health and also ensure that resource allocation is provided with considered economic, social and community benefits. </description>
      <description type="brief">Supportive care needs assessment has gained acceptance as a clinically important outcome due to its ability to assess identify individuals and/or groups needs and identify the magnitude of need allowing prioritisation by services. Indigenous people experience more aggressive cancers and a higher cancer mortality rate than their non-Indigenous counterparts. Outcomes like support needs have been shown to predict survival. Despite this, existing needs assessment tools have not been validated in an Indigenous cancer population, nor are there any needs assessment measures which incorporate Indigenous-specific questionnaire items. We propose to conduct a validation study of an existing cancer patients supportive care needs assessment tool.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100158</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100158</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100158</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Climate change research: Can Sydney rock oysters adapt to chronic multigenerational exposure to ocean acidification and temperature?</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-485355</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">ECOLOGICAL APPLICATIONS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms Laura M Parker; A/Prof Pauline M Ross; A/Prof David A Raftos; Dr Wayne A O'Connor; Prof Dr Hans O Portner
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 199,988.00
Application Year: 2009
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Our goal is to understand how long term exposure to climate change will affect oysters in an effort to climate-proof the Australian oyster industry. Oyster farming is worth more than $1 billion a year in retail sales and employs thousands of Australians. The future of this industry is threatened by climate change, particularly its impact on the reproduction and development of oysters. Our study will identify how oysters respond to chronic multigenerational exposure to ocean acidification and temperature, &amp; identify physiological mechanisms and genes associated with climate change adaptation. This work will maintain Australia's position at the forefront of climate change research on marine ecosystems.</description>
      <description type="brief">This project will identify the chronic multigenerational response of an iconic oyster species to ocean acidification (OA) &amp; temperature. Already acute studies have found impacts of OA &amp; temperature on the reproduction &amp; development of oysters with selectively bred oyster populations being resilient. We have no information internationally on the impact of long term exposure to OA &amp; temperature on marine organisms &amp; ecosystems. We will use chronic multigenerational experiments to identify whether populations of the Sydney rock oyster have the potential to adapt to OA &amp; temperature. Our goal is to determine how the Australian oyster industry will be affected by climate change &amp; develop strategies for the sustainability of marine ecosystems.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775809</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775809</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775809</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Patterns of Engagement: The Contexts, Frequency and Characteristics of Psychological Practice with Indigenous Clients</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-574210</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">PSYCHOLOGY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms W Nolan; A/Prof K McConnochie; Dr RJ Ranzijn
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 28,000.00
Application Year: 2006
First Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">The extent and debilitating nature of Indigenous mental health problems has been widely documented. National and community benefits will derive from the development of strategies enabling psychologists to work more effectively with Indigenous clients to improve their psychological and social well-being and resolve mental health problems. The project will identify how psychologists currently work with Indigenous clients, which will provide data to guide the development of effective strategies to bring about change.</description>
      <description type="brief">Despite widespread assertions that psychologists adopt culturally inappropriate strategies for working with Indigenous clients in a wide range of forensic, clinical and social contexts, there is no empirical evidence describing the characteristics of this engagement or the nature of external or internal constraints to change. This project will document the contexts, frequency and characteristics of the engagement of psychologists working with Indigenous clients and the external and intrinsic factors which constrain these interactions. This will provide base-line data against which the effectiveness of professional development activities and the impact of policy and paradigm changes can be assessed.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561903</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561903</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561903</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence for Vision Science</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-595489</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">NEUROSCIENCES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof TD Lamb; Prof J Stone; Prof MV Srinivasan; Dr M Edwards; Dr MR Ibbotson; Dr AC James; A/Prof TL Maddess; A/Prof IG Morgan; A/Prof JM Provis; Dr K Valter-Kocsi; A/Prof J Zeil; Dr S Zhang; Prof D Yu; Dr SJ Cringle; Prof DI Vaney; Prof B Dreher; Prof S Bisti; Dr PI Corke; Prof Dr M Egelhaaf; Prof D Floreano; Dr RD Hamer; Mr B Meek; Dr M Mustari; Prof Y Nagai; Dr HS Vanni; Prof JM Zanker; Prof A Zelinsky
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 16,250,000.00
Application Year: 2004
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This Centre will generate important new knowledge of the performance, logic and stability of vision and visual behaviour. This knowledge will help reduce the burden of vision impairment in Australia, increasing productivity, promoting healthy ageing and reducing the community costs of visual impairment (ca. $9.85 billion in 2004). The knowledge produced will also make possible world-class innovations in robotics, leading to novel automated vision systems with applications in industry and national security. Other knowledge will develop novel diagnostic technologies, for application in health delivery.

</description>
      <description type="brief">Vision is our most powerful sense, and blindness is a severe loss, yet increasingly common as the population ages. This Centre of Excellence will explore three themes: the extraordinary sensitivity and adaptability of vision; how vision forms the basis for behaviour; and why vision fails, especially with age. One major outcome will be fundamental understanding of retinal mechanisms and brain algorithms of vision. A second will be the application of this knowledge to the design of autonomous visually-guided robots (e.g. flying machines). A third outcome will be understanding of the stability and degeneration of the retina and eye, laying the scientific foundation for diagnosis and therapy in a range of age-related blinding diseases.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208022</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208022</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208022</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">On Becoming a Middle School Teacher: Reclaiming the Wasteland of the Middle Years of Schooling</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593299</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">EDUCATION STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof J Smyth
Scheme: Discovery Projects
Funding: $AUD 225,000.00
Application Year: 2001
First Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">This project aims to investigate how teachers in Australian government schools committed to the middle years of schooling (ages 14?16), are ?reinventing? their teaching in the current policy reform context. The research will explore how policies support or hinder teachers in establishing and sustaining educative relationships with young adolescents. Detailed ethnographic case studies will examine how teachers restructure and reculture what schools do to better serve students who are increasingly ?at risk?. The project will provide crucial understandings into the theory, policy and practice of teaching necessary to enable all young adolescents to experience a rewarding high school education.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775793</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775793</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775793</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">The extent of competition between the native and introduced herbivores of Kangaroo Island.</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-460832</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">ECOLOGY AND EVOLUTION</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr RJ Bosworth; Dr PG Stott; A/Prof GS Howarth
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 85,800.00
Application Year: 2006
First Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This project examines grazing behaviour and competition among native and introduced herbivores to optimise limited resources in an ecologically fragile environment. The project will provide a biological basis for the development of management strategies to provide positive outcomes for the Kangaroo Island environment and potential economic benefit to the local and national economy. Environmental benefit includes the reduction of total grazing pressure on pastures and native vegetation of Kangaroo Island, which is one of Australia&#x2019;s top 15 biodiversity &#x2018;hot spots&#x2019;, and thus help with conservation efforts on Kangaroo Island. Economic benefit will follow if farmers receive income from a currently wasted resource.</description>
      <description type="brief">The aim is to determine whether co-existing herbivores can be managed by avoidance of competition through size exclusion (Hutchinson theory). In particular, we want to explore whether the Hutchinson theory of interspecific competition applies to the grazing mammals of Kangaroo Island. The project is significant due to the conservation value of the habitat, the potential to improve the management of both domestic and wildlife herbivores and because it incorporates the first experimental tests of Hutchinson's theory. Present literature that examined the theory used only anecdotal evidence. This study will incorporate observational data collection, manipulative field experiments and rigorous pen trials to test the Hutchinson theory.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348228</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348228</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348228</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence for Autonomous Systems</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593941</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">INTERDISCIPLINARY ENGINEERING</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof HF Durrant-WhyteProf CA SammutProf G DissanayakeA/Prof EM Nebot
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 15,200,000.00
Application Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">The aim of the Centre is to research and explore intelligence in autonomous systems. The Centre will undertake fundamental research organised around four themes; perception, control, learning and systems. These themes will interact through two research demonstrators focused around a built environment and a natural outdoor environment. The Centre brings together a critical mass of over 70 staff and research students from three leading research groups. The partners also have substantial track record in the commercial exploitation of autonomous systems. The proposed Centre offers the potential of growing into the world's leading autonomous systems research centre.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775813</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775813</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775813</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Bringing indigenous knowledge into early childhood settings</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-641982</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT OF TEACHERS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms LM Ford; Dr D Szarkowicz
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 70,000.00
Application Year: 2006
First Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This project will produce a negotiated model of Indigenous teaching and learning in early childhood settings by documenting the diversity of Indigenous knowledge from the Northern Territory.  This model will be suitable for sharing with Indigenous and non-Indigenous children within the early childhood sector.  Through this sharing there can be a greater recognition and acceptance of the knowledge Indigenous children bring to early childhood programs, a facilitation of understanding in non-Indigenous children and assist in the maintenance of this knowledge for future generations.  </description>
      <description type="brief">This research aims to identify and document appropriate Indigenous knowledge from the Central and Top End regions of the Northern Territory, Australia. The knowledge identified will be that which is appropriate to share with children in all early childhood settings, irrespective of cultural background. Both relevant Indigenous knowledge and appropriate strategies for teaching such will be investigated and disseminated.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561787</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561787</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561787</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence in Coherent X-ray Science</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593909</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">OTHER PHYSICAL SCIENCES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof KA Nugent; Prof L Tilley; Dr LV Dao; Prof RA Lewis; Dr TA Smith; Dr AG Peele; Prof P Hannaford; Dr MT Ryan; Dr AY Nikulin; Dr JN Varghese; Dr SW Wilkins; Dr JM Gulbis; Dr T Ishikawa; Prof HO Moser; Dr RF Garrett; Dr IL McNulty; Dr H Chapman; A/Prof J Miao
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 16,700,000.00
Application Year: 2004
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">The twenty first century is said to be the century of biology. And there is no doubt that the development of our understanding of biological system is continuing at a massive rate. However as our understanding deepens, we need to draw on the whole range of scientific disciplines to proceed. This Centre draws together a multidisciplinary team of world-leading scientists to address one the key questions in modern biology, the structure of a membrane protein. We will develop techniques based on the latest developments in theoretical physics &amp; chemistry, imaging, biology and technology ? including the new Australian Synchrotron ? to create new approaches to structural biology.</description>
      <description type="brief">X-ray sources are becoming ever brighter, and x-ray lasers will be available in the next ten years. These sources will open up whole new areas of investigation such as the structural determination of proteins not amenable to conventional methods. This centre will bring physicists, chemists and biologists together to develop fundamentally new approaches to probing biological structures and processes. We combine world-class expertise in imaging, structural biology, laser science and molecular theory. The project will develop novel high resolution imaging and probing using the Australian Synchrotron, and ultimately x-ray lasers. The overarching scientific aim of the centre is the determination the structure of a membrane protein.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348193</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348193</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348193</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre for Structural and Functional Microbial Genomics</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-507067</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">MICROBIOLOGY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof B AdlerProf DE TaylorProf RL CoppelA/Prof JK DaviesA/Prof RJ DevenishProf P NagleyProf JI RoodDr J RossjohnDr JC Whisstock
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 4,897,495.00
Application Year: 2002
First Year: 2003
</description>
      <description type="brief">Australian Primary Industry will benefit from a team of experts in microbial genetics, bioinformatics and protein structure and function undertaking integrated studies on microbial genomics and phenomics that are focused on fundamental biological processes and host/pathogen interactions. Whole genome expression and protein profiling will be used to characterise genes whose expression is altered in the infected host and to analyse genes involved in the control of key cellular processes. The Centre will also determine the shapes of key molecules and their interactions. Practical outcomes will include new veterinary vaccines and the identification of novel antimicrobial targets.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348259</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348259</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348259</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence for Ultrahigh-bandwidth Devices for Optical Systems</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593941</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">COMMUNICATIONS TECHNOLOGIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr CM de SterkeDr BJ EggletonProf YS KivsharDr JL BlowsProf LC BottenDr JM DawesProf M GuDr WZ KrolikowskiProf B Luther-DaviesProf RC McPhedranProf JA PiperDr MJ WithfordProf S KawataDr K KruszelnickiProf K RichardsonDr R SlusherProf G Tayeb
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Application Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">The Centre, through a ground-breaking research program, will in the next five years invent and develop a set of revolutionary optical devices and will integrate these devices onto a photonic chip, for the use in the next generation of ultra-high bandwidth optical telecommunications systems. These systems will dramatically improve online services to the Australian community in key areas such as health, education and business connectivity. Australia's high tech industry will benefit from the commercialisation opportunities arising from the Centre's research, and also from the creation of a pool of highly skilled ICT professionals.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348250</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348250</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348250</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence for Quantum Computer Technology</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593921</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">THEORETICAL AND CONDENSED MATTER PHYSICS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof RG ClarkProf GJ MilburnA/Prof AS DzurakA/Prof MY SimmonsDr AR HamiltonProf S PrawerA/Prof DN JamiesonA/Prof LC HollenbergDr JC McCallumDr CI PakesProf H Rubinsztein-DunlopDr TC RalphDr AG WhiteProf BC SandersDr HM WisemanProf DR McKenzieDr D Pulford
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Application Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">Development of a quantum computer (QC) for massively parallel computing is one of the major challenges in science and engineering this century. Since 2000 the Centre has achieved two major breakthroughs in this field: constructing the key functional element of a silicon solid-state QC; and co-inventing a scheme for efficient linear optics QC. The proposed CoE aims to align these two nationally co-ordinated research programs with the world?s existing computer and IT industries to realise a fault-tolerant multiple qubit quantum processor with integrated control and qubit chips, and develop a scaleable optical quantum processor providing significant economic benefit to Australia.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348239</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348239</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348239</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence in Biotechnology and Development</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-565275</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">GENETICS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof RJ AitkenDr KL LovelandProf PA KoopmanA/Prof AH SinclairProf DM De KretserDr M O'BryanDr GR HimeProf DA JansDr SD RomanDr EA McLaughlinProf C GoodnowProf MK Holland
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 15,878,900.00
Application Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">The Centre will create a multidisciplinary research team focusing on the molecular mechanisms that drive the specification and differentiation of male germ cells. This research will improve our fundamental understanding of how complex regulatory networks control the expression of a complex phenotype, the spermatozoon. It will also create a platform of knowledge from which we can stimulate the growth of the Australian Biotechnology industry, the protection of the Australian Environment and the well-being of the Australian people. Key issues for this Centre include testicular cancer, male infertility, contraception, pest animal control, environmental impacts on human health and gene pharming.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208030</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208030</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208030</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">The Role of C-kit and Selected TGF beta Family Members in Recruitment</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-507067</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">GENETICS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr S Cox A/Prof G Jenkin Dr JM Shaw Dr T Goto
Scheme: Discovery Projects
Funding: $AUD 237,000.00
Application Year: 2001
First Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">The recruitment of primordial follicles into the growth phase is central to female reproductive function, however the control of this process to date, has been poorly understood due to inadequate technologies. Our team has recently developed novel recruitment models and a new and innovative method of isolating primordial follicles which will enable us to identify the role of c-kit and selected TGF beta family members in recruitment. This work will provide cornerstone scientific knowledge about the control of female reproduction and provide the impetus for the development of more effective contraception and superovulation strategies in mammals.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989457</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989457</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989457</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Digitisation and Indigenous Communities: A study of the development of online collections. The interface between international institutions and Australian Indigenous communities.</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593909</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">CURATORIAL STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr LC Ormond-Parker; Prof ML Langton; A/Prof RJ Sloggett
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 48,000.00
Application Year: 2008
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">The preservation and protection of Australian Indigenous knowledge in the digital age is in the National interest.  This research may offer much valued insight into the ways in which Indigenous people are engaging in the protection of traditional knowledge in Australia in the digital age. At the international level has seen the start of  development at the World Intellectual Property Organisation into the  International legal mechanisms concerning the protection of traditional knowledge and the intellectual property aspects of access to and benefit-sharing from such knowledge. This study will explore these important developments which are in Australia's national interest. </description>
      <description type="brief">The research explores ways in which Indigenous communities are utilising and managing their cultural heritage resources and local knowledge in the digital age. Institutions around the globe are increasingly turning to digitisation as a way of ordering and preserving their vast collections. This is a study about the way in which communities are focusing on the repatriation of digital material, their relationships and interactions with institutions that hold their material cultural and traditional knowledge and the development of online collections. The study is important in shaping co-operative approaches and interactions between institutions and indigenous communities though the use of innovative technology.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0240329</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0240329</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0240329</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Living in Harmony: A case study on Aboriginal Mental Health Promotion to develop an understanding of the capacity of Indigenous Australians</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-484876</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">PUBLIC HEALTH AND HEALTH SERVICES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms A Poelina A/Prof D Plummer Dr AJ Madison Dr A Singh
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 62,310.00
Application Year: 2001
First Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">Mental health problems in Australian Indigenous peoples are a major public health issue: the are frequent, disabling and represent a significant health burden. Indigenous Australian peoples and communities share a number of common historical and socio-economic experiences, and also differ one from another in terms of culture, language and tradition. However, the core concepts of mental health may have sufficiently similar characteristic and process across the communities. This ethnographic case study approach will provide i) a process for culturally mapping how Nyikina-Mangala people conceptualise 'mental health' and ii) develop culturally appropriate mental health promotion and prevention programs for indigenous communities.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208038</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208038</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208038</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Institutional transitions to sustainable agriculture: An inter-disciplinary analysis of a novel common-property resource governance system</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-484876</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">SOCIOLOGY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr DJ Brunckhorst Dr NC Reid Dr OJ Cacho Dr lA Lobry de Bruyn  Dr TJ Lynch Mr G Marshall
Scheme: Discovery Projects
Funding: $AUD 202,225.00
Application Year: 2001
First Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">Efforts to overcome the severe degradation of land resources supporting agriculture and human communities continue to be constrained by institutions and social norms. The knowledge needed for a transition to sustainable agricultural landscapes through institutional change is inadequate. A collaboration between specialists in economics, politics, sociology, ecology and soil science at the University of New England and graziers in an upper Murray-Darling subcatchment will analyse the transition to a common-property institution on this subcatchment. It will make a distinctively Australian contribution to international efforts to understand such transitions, and serve as a model for progress towards sustainability elsewhere in Australia.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989055</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989055</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989055</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Private Sector Workplace Employment Programs for Indigenous Australians</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-565275</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">BUSINESS AND MANAGEMENT</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mrs SM Dyer; Prof KJ Burgess; Prof J Maynard
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 55,000.00
Application Year: 2008
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">The research examines the workplace programs aimed at Indigenous employment in the top 50 companies in Australia. It identifies workplace conditions and policies that govern the success of such programs and provides a benchmark for workplace program development to assist Indigenous Australians, one of the most disadvantaged groups in the labour market. </description>
      <description type="brief">Aims: To map workplace programs provided by the top 50 listed companies for Indigenous Australians. To undertake detailed case studies of selected workplace programs for Indigenous Australians. To examine policies and conditions that are conducive to succesful outcomes. Significance: fills a gap in the analysis of workplace programs for Indigenous Australians. Outcomes: informed development of workplace programs for Indigenous Australians.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775816</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775816</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775816</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Building Teachers' Assessment Capacity to Engage Indigenous Learners</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-642603</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">EDUCATION STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms CA Fisher; Prof V Klenowski; A/Prof SC McGinty
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 30,000.00
Application Year: 2006
First Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This highly significant study will provide much needed understanding about how to build more equitable assessment practices to address the major problem of underperforming Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander students in regional and remote Australia.  The anticipated outcomes will advance knowledge to include more culturally fair assessment practices.  National and state policies now require teachers to use standards-referenced reporting which this study will explore using related intervention strategies.  Pedagogic and assessment approaches to improve young Indigenous Australians' educational performance will help them succeed in schooling and in acquiring skills for a more secure economic, social and cultural future.</description>
      <description type="brief">This project responds to the government's assessment policies which require the use of standards for reporting student achievement. An urgent need exists to provide teachers with culturally-relevant teaching and assessment practices to engage Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander students. This project will contribute knowledge about how teachers judge the quality of student work, derived from culturally-relevant assessment strategies, using common state-wide standards for reporting. Social process moderation will help ensure that reliability and standards are not compromised. Educators, policy makers and the wider community will benefit from evidence that informs reporting and improves educational outcomes for Indigenous students.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882472</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882472</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882472</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Bubalamai Bawa Gumada. Healing the Wounds of the Heart: A Research-Based Intervention Diminishing the Impact of Racism and Stereotype Threat</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-485355</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">EDUCATION STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr GH Bodkin-Andrews; Prof RG Craven; Dr AS Yeung
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 180,000.00
Application Year: 2007
First Year: 2008
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Indigenous students are not achieving academic outcomes commensurate with non-Indigenous peers. Although research has identified contributing factors, little is known of the effect of cultural stereotypes on Indigenous students' academic outcomes. This research will implement an innovative new intervention to address stereotyping in secondary schools for Indigenous students and evaluate the intervention's impact on mental health and academic functioning. This research offers important educational and socio-economic benefits by enriching the psychosocial adjustment and life potential of Indigenous Australians. This will foster schools free from racism and stereotyping that will contribute to individual, community, and national wellbeing.</description>
      <description type="brief">Stereotype-Threat is where a minority group member is affected by, or internalizes, negative social stereotypes or racist generalizations held against their group as a whole. Research has found that stereotype threat can impact upon minority group members' academic outcomes. Grounded on cutting-edge interdisciplinary theory and research I will: develop age-appropriate psychosocial outcome measures; explicate psychosocial consequences of stereotype-threat and racism; and implement an innovative intervention to address stereotype-threat and racism in secondary schools for Indigenous students and evaluate its impact on mental health and academic functioning using a powerful experimental design and state-of-the-art multi-method analyses.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775833</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775833</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775833</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Aboriginal Women Law and Colonialism: Safe Places for Women.</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593941</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">LAW</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr I Watson; A/Prof J Stubbs
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 40,000.00
Application Year: 2006
First Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">There has been extensive media reporting on violent crimes against Aboriginal women and children in Aboriginal communities across Australia, which has created wide public debate.  In particular the role of the courts when sentencing Aboriginal offenders of violent crimes has drawn attention to the interpretation of Aboriginal law and culture.  The evaluation of Australian case law will be invaluable in expanding the Australian communities knowledge in this area of law and policy, in planning safer Aboriginal communities for Aboriginal women and children in the future.    </description>
      <description type="brief">This project will collect, collate and analyse Australian case law from the 1820s until 1985, complementing the Chief Investigator's current review of Australian cases from 1986 to 2006. In light of the recent debate on violent crimes against Aboriginal women this project will review Australian cases that have considered questions of Aboriginal law, culture and violence against Aboriginal women, throughout Australian legal history. The decisions will be analysed to consider the courts interpretation of Aboriginal law and culture. This analysis will provide information for the framing of future conversations and policy directions concerning the safety of Aboriginal women and children.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0667638</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0667638</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0667638</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Brassinosteroids and Water Stresses</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-460913</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">BOTANY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms CE Jager; Prof JB Reid
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 166,080.00
Application Year: 2005
First Year: 2006
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Water use has become a major factor affecting agricultural development in Australia. Therefore, it is important to develop new techniques to sustain crop production in today's climate. Developing a clearer understanding of brassinosteroids, their underlying role in water stresses and their interaction with known stress-related hormones, such as abscisic acid and ethylene, will eventually enable more effective and efficient manipulation of plant growth in water stressed areas. This project has the added advantage of working with a legume, a group of plants that make a substantial contribution to the Australian economy. Our increased knowledge of legume development will help underpin future growth of this sector.</description>
      <description type="brief">Brassinosteroids are steroid hormones that are essential for normal plant growth and development. It has been suggested that the application of brassinosteroids increases the plant's resistance to stress. This project will determine whether endogenous brassinosteroids are involved in water stresses and whether increased or decreased brassinosteroid levels help plants cope better under drought or waterlogged conditions. The project will also examine the interactions that may occur between brassinosteroids and known stress-related hormones, such as abscisic acid and ethylene. This research will help to elucidate the hormonal control of water stresses (both drought and waterlogging), which will ultimately benefit agricultural techniques.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0240614</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0240614</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0240614</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Indigenous Tourism in the South West Region of Western Australia: a case study analysis from a Nyungar Perspective</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-589763</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">TOURISM</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr L Collard Em/Prof GC Bolton
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 82,200.00
Application Year: 2001
First Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">This proposal seeks to: create a southern Australian Indigenous Tourism inventory that emphasises the distinct regional tourism characteristics and preferences. This would be the first academic research undertaking of its kind in this area; establish a series of case studies and best practice scenarios that highlight regional opportunities; and identify relevant ?partnerships? that support Nyungar tourist development both from mainstream and Aboriginal partners; establish a web site to act as a WA resource for Indigenous tourism operations. The website will include relevant links to existing databases such as Aboriginal Traders Alliance (NSW) and Aboriginal Art and Culture Centre (NT).</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882469</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882469</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882469</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Hidden Talent: A Critical Analysis of the Contributions of Aboriginal Musicians of the New England Tablelands to Contemporary Aboriginal Culture and Cultural Revitalisation</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-485355</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">OTHER STUDIES IN HUMAN SOCIETY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr P McKenzie; Prof MJ Atherton; Prof RG Craven
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 105,000.00
Application Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">My research will add a fresh historical study by an Indigenous researcher to the literature by undertaking a critical multi-method analysis of Anaiwan people's contributions to the development of music in the New England Tablelands to contemporary Aboriginal culture and cultural revitalisation. Their stories have yet to be told, documented, analysed, and shared with all Australians. The significantly different life histories these musicians have lived and the impact of their music contributions on the community will contribute to an engaging public history.</description>
      <description type="brief">My research will form a significant contribution to the Anaiwan Nation and to Australians' understanding of the development of Aboriginal music in the New England area. There has been very little research into this aspect of my people's history. The research aims to make a significant contribution to our conceptual understandings of and documentation of Australian history from an Indigenous perspective to ensure Indigenous historical interpretations and perspectives are voiced in critical academic analyses of Australian history. The outcome will be a comprehensive multimethod critical analysis of Anaiwan people's contributions to the development of music in the New England area.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348221</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348221</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348221</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre for Bioinformatics</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-460867</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">GENETICS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof MA RaganDr TL BaileyProf K BurrageDr Y ChenA/Prof GP DobsonProf J DrennanDr MR FellowsDr SM GrimmondDr JS HallinanDr M HeglandDr P KodaliProf GJ McLachlanDr BJ MarshDr RM MuhlbergerDr LK NielsenProf BA PailthorpeDr I RigoutsosDr RD Teasdale
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 7,260,835.00
Application Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">The Australian Centre for Genome-Phenome Bioinformatics will examine how the genome comes to life in the mammalian cell during differentiation and development. We will model, visualise and experimentally validate the complex cellular systems and regulatory networks that control the transformation of genomic information into biological structure and function. We will develop novel approaches and tools to improve health, optimise agricultural production and exploit new cell technologies. The Centre will build critical mass and national focus in bioinformatics to generate the human capital and intellectual property that Australia needs to compete in advanced bioscience and biotechnology.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208042</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208042</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208042</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">The Evolution of East Asian Regionalism</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-465942</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">POLITICAL SCIENCE</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr MK Beeson
Scheme: Discovery Projects
Funding: $AUD 24,000.00
Application Year: 2001
First Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">In the aftermath of the East Asian crisis of 1997, the countries of East Asia have embarked upon a self-consciously pursued project of political integration or regionalism. If successful, it will have profound implications for the region?s internal and external relations, and future development. This project will examine how regionalism is evolving in this strategically pivotal area, detail the factors that are encouraging or obstructing this process, and provide a more appropriate theoretical framework in which to understand East Asia?s highly distinctive style of regional integration.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0348095</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0348095</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0348095</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">The Intersubjectivity of Race in the Social and Personal Construction of Identity and Self Identification</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593921</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">PHILOSOPHY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms D Davis Dr R Diprose
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 20,000.00
Application Year: 2002
First Year: 2003
</description>
      <description type="brief">The project will investigate the social construction of race and identity. Its aim is to demonstrate how race operates as an external and prescriptive marker, which is internalised and performed; and how race intersects with other factors operating on the construction of identity. This notion challenges many standard accounts, and provides a new and innovative framework for analysing race and identity. The project draws on work and theories rarely used in analysing racial identity in Australia, and applies them in new and innovative ways. The expected outcomes include resolution of problems of difference in race and identity, within race theory.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0239285</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0239285</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0239285</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Aboriginal art history and tradition in the West Kimberley region, Western Australia: Representations and constructions of place, space and identity.</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593909</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">ANTHROPOLOGY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms CA Coyne Prof M Langton
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 15,000.00
Application Year: 2001
First Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">There is a paucity of research on the topic of Aboriginal art history in the West Kimberley coast. This project aims to investigate how Aboriginal art styles have been influenced by European settlement and ideas during the last century in this region. The chief investigator will survey the historical record, examine collections of material cultural objects and the artworks held in Australian museums, and conduct fieldwork in the region. The project will result in the first comprehensive account of the art traditions in Aboriginal Communities of the area with anticipated outcomes of field reports, journal publications and a PhD thesis.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882815</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882815</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0882815</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Conditions for Success to Enhance Aboriginal Education</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-485355</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">OTHER STUDIES IN HUMAN SOCIETY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms L Riley-Mundine; Prof RG Craven; Dr GE Munns
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 105,000.00
Application Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Aboriginal students remain the most educationally disadvantaged Australians. This research will elucidate the conditions for success in classrooms, schools, and Aboriginal communities that empower primary Aboriginal students to achieve their potential. The outcomes of this research have the potential to 'break the cycle' of underachievement by generating new solutions to: strengthen schooling; shape a better future for Aboriginal students by enabling students to reach their potential; build capacity at community, school, classroom, and individual levels; and providing educators with effective strategies that are salient to Aboriginal children for doing so.</description>
      <description type="brief">Aboriginal students remain the most educationally disadvantaged Australians. Interventions have often failed to penetrate the classroom door and as such educators are unable to help Aboriginal students achieve commensurate educational outcomes as their non-Indigenous peers. This research seeks to elucidate the conditions for success for primary Aboriginal students to achieve effective academic achievement, school engagement, wellbeing, and participation outcomes at the individual; classroom; school, home, and community levels. This will result in building the capacity of Aboriginal Education, schooling, and communities and contribute to Aboriginal students fulfilling their full potential.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775822</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775822</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775822</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Elder Assessments of Early Material Culture Collections from Arnhem Land and Contemporary Access Needs to Them among Their Source Communities</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593941</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">CULTURAL STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr JN Gumbula; Dr AD Corn
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 245,000.00
Application Year: 2006
First Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">There is enormous interest in Arnhem Land about the region's recorded history. In recent years, the return of digital materials from collections worldwide has become a significant and efficacious strategy for stimulating cultural maintenance there. The sense of history that these materials bring is proving invaluable in maintaining well-being and community in Arnhem Land amid the hardships of local life. Informed by custodians of the region's endangered languages and traditions, this project will produce findings of world heritage significance that will articulate the collections access needs of local people. It would be the first ARC project to be led by a Yolngu Elder.</description>
      <description type="brief">Drawing on my expertise as a Yolngu Elder with research experience in material culture, this project will assess historical materials from Arnhem Land at the University of Sydney Archives. The Elkin Personal Archive includes materials recorded by Webb and Warner at Milinginbi dating from 1922, and are the oldest known from Arnhem Land. I will explore this collection with reference to traditional intellectual frameworks that still guide community life in Arnhem Land, and to its links to other collections worldwide. I will work consultatively with these collections to develop appropriate measures and find new technologies that will assist them in meeting the mounting access needs of source communities to their resources.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100200</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100200</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100200</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Reversing the gaze: Indigenous perspectives on cultural representation in national museums</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">CURATORIAL AND RELATED STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr Sandy T O'Sullivan; Prof Peter M Stephenson; A/Prof Lyn Fasoli
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 177,000.00
Application Year: 2009
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Through a focus on new media and digital engagements the project will identify the capacity for Indigenous communities to act as partners in their representation in the national museum space.  By contributing an indigenous-centred review of best-practice moments at both a national and international level, the project will deliver modes of engagement that will benefit both Indigenous communities and museums engaged in Indigenous cultural representation.</description>
      <description type="brief">The aim of the project is to provide for Indigenous communities, museums and those invested in the collaboration between these groups, a comprehensive review of best-practice moments in new media, interactive displays and in the online exhibition of Indigenous cultural representation in major mainstream museums. The project will focus on exhibitions identified by the Indigenous participants, and will be carried out from an Indigenous perspective. The project will demonstrate the capacity for mainstream museums to encourage and facilitate a curatorial process that enables Indigenous individuals and communities to have genuine input and control over their own presentation.</description>
      <description type="institution">Batchelor Institute of Indigenous Tertiary Education</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561495</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561495</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561495</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence - In Plant Energy Biology (CPEB)</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-464686</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">BOTANY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: A/Prof JM Whelan; Prof S Smith; Prof MR Badger; Dr ID Small; Dr AH Millar; Prof DA Day; Dr BJ Pogson
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 22,300,000.00
Application Year: 2004
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Plant cell metabolism underlies the synthesis of important products in crops, and subtle changes in metabolism can enhance germination rates, early seedling vigour, biomass/yield, and tolerance to harsh environments. Research in CPEB will focus on control of this metabolism. Its expertise will enhance Australia's participation in major international research efforts directly relevant to sustainable agriculture in a country with fragile/degrading ecosystems. The research will provide new approaches for enhancing quality metabolite traits important for human health. It will further strengthen our international leadership in plant energy science, and will strengthen Australia's research training in systems biology to influence plant function.</description>
      <description type="brief">Plants are sources of many essential products, including food, fuels, and vitamins. These products result from energy metabolism in sub-cellular compartments (organelles) called mitochondria, chloroplasts and peroxisomes. CPEB aims to discover and characterise molecular components and control mechanisms that underpin plant energy metabolism using functional genomic analysis. Knowing the factors that control biogenesis of these organelles will better enable the breeding of plants with specified metabolic traits. Benefits include enhanced control of biomass and yield, water and nutrient efficiency, synthesis of nutrients important for human and animal health, and plants better able to tolerate the environmental stresses of Australia.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0347624</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0347624</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0347624</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Dreaming Tracks and Trading Paths - a study of Aboriginal trading routes through Queensland</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-465942</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">OTHER STUDIES IN HUMAN SOCIETY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr D Kerwin Dr RJ Ganter
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 20,022.00
Application Year: 2002
First Year: 2003
</description>
      <description type="brief">Aboriginal song lines and trade routes became the foundation for stock routes, coach ways and bitumen highways because successful European exploration used the expediency of Aboriginal guides who travelled along the routes already familiar to them. These routes are documented in instruments of land management such as churingas, toas or shields, and in the mnemotic memory of songs and stories. By reading together these two types of knowledge - of European exploration and of Aboriginal authorship of country - popular ways of 'knowing Aborigines' become fundamentally reinscribed and much popular knowledge about Aboriginal societies is deeply challenged.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100130</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100130</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100130</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Developing predictive tools for rapid assessment of multiple impacts, including climate change, on the marine ecosystem of Torres Strait (Australia)</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-642603</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">ECOLOGICAL APPLICATIONS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms Cass M Hunter; Dr James R Butler; Mr Timothy D Skewes; Mr David T Brewer; Dr Vincent Lyne; Prof Stephen M Turton
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 180,834.00
Application Year: 2009
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This project will underpin Australia's long-term commitment to maintain environmental biodiversity and sustainability in the face of synergistic effects from multiple threats. We will describe the consequences of threats and stressors on marine processes, harvested resources, and ecosystem functioning by identifying vulnerable species and habitats. We will provide management advice on balancing cultural and ecosystem integrity, economic efficiency, and ecosystem resilience under scenarios of climate and environmental change. This information is of immediate use by Australian government agencies. The project will put Australian scientists at the forefront of research focused on the adaptation of marine ecosystems to synergistic effects.</description>
      <description type="brief">Australia's unique marine biodiversity and significant economic wealth generated from marine systems are particularly vulnerable to the threat of climate change and other anthropogenic threats. Currently, the science needed to manage the synergistic effects of multiple threats lags far behind our current knowledge of the biophysical components of marine ecosystems. We will develop tools to link threats and ecosystem processes to predict the impact that exposure has on marine life. This will provide an understanding of the strategies that can be applied to protect biodiversity, increase resilience of marine ecosystems, and provide sustained cultural and economic benefit for Australian communities under climate and environmental change.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0668388</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0668388</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0668388</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">The genetic basis for bioactivity in the traditional medicine plants of Australia</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593921</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">MICROBIOLOGY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr SD Ingrey; A/Prof BA Neilan
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 87,458.00
Application Year: 2005
First Year: 2006
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">A plant species that produces a bioactive compound usually produce the compound in very small amounts. To allow for marketable levels of production of the bioactive compound, numerous amounts of plants would need to be removed from the environment. This not only removes the limited supply of possibly rare types of plants from the environment but also denies the use of this plant by traditional people. Locating and using the genes responsible for producing these bioactive compounds will allow their sustainable biosynthesis.</description>
      <description type="brief">Ethnobotany is the study of the mutual relationship between plants and traditional people. Australian Aboriginals use a range of plants from their tribal lands for their medicinal purposes. Nonribosomal peptide synthetases (NRPS) and polyketide synthases (PKS) are two enzyme complexes that are involved in the biosynthesis of many bioactive compounds. Plant species that are used from the Dharawal tribal area as well as other tribes from around Australia will be screened for the NRPS and PKS genes. Activity will be assessed by mass spectrometry, as well as by antibacterial, antifungal, antiviral and anticancer assays.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561616</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561616</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0561616</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence for Electromaterials Science</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-464691</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">PHYSICAL CHEMISTRY (INCL. STRUCTURAL)</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof GG Wallace; Prof DL Officer; Prof DR MacFarlane; Prof GM Clark; Prof M Forsyth; Prof LA Kane-Maguire; Dr PC Innis; Prof GM Spinks; Prof HR Brown; Dr CO Too; A/Prof WE Price; Prof HK Liu; Dr L Spiccia; A/Prof SM Dodds; Dr PA Keller; Dr AI Minett; Dr Y Cheng; Dr G Alici; Dr RM Kapsa
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 19,700,000.00
Application Year: 2004
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">The Centre will tackle some of the biggest challenges facing society: those of renewable energy,  sustainable industries and enhancing human health.  Improvements in all these areas are possible by developing electromaterials with improved efficiency in the generation and transfer of electrical charge.  By developing new nano-materials and new theories to explain their behaviour, the Centre will make advances in the areas of human health through the regeneration of damaged nerves (eg. in spinal injury) and development of artificial muscles; in renewable energy (plastic solar cells, lightweight batteries and electronic textiles) and in sustainable industries (recovery of precious metals and new corrosion protection technologies).</description>
      <description type="brief">The Australian Centre for Electromaterials Science brings together eminent scientists to develop the nano-science and nano-technology related to the movement of electric charge within and between materials. Such processes are fundamentally important to a diverse array of phenomena important in many biological and industrial processes. The exciting new developments in nanoscale materials offer the potential for groundbreaking improvements in charge generation and transfer. However, there is a general lack of understanding of these processes at the nano domain. The new Centre will study these processes, develop improved electromaterials and apply these materials in biomedicine, industrial processes, energy harvesting and energy storage.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348217</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348217</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348217</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence for Mathematical and Statistical Modelling of Complex Systems</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593909</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">STATISTICS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof AJ GuttmannProf PG TaylorDr AL OwczarekA/Prof K BorovkovA/Prof A XiaDr R BrakProf PG HallProf CC HeydeProf AH DooleyProf IH SloanProf C RogersA/Prof GR QuispelDr PK Pollett
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 15,861,051.00
Application Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">This Centre, formed by a group of high-profile researchers, brings expertise from linked but hitherto disparate areas together. It will place Australia at the forefront of research into complex systems. The mission of the Centre is to stimulate research in mathematical and statistical modelling of complex systems and to encourage cross-fertilisation of ideas and techniques. The specific objectives are - to formulate and analyse mathematical and statistical models for natural and artificial complex systems, - to use these models to develop an understanding of the behaviour of these systems - to incorporate this understanding into strategies for management and control.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775792</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775792</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775792</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Aboriginal identities within architecture and the built environment: Perceptions of a sample of Indigenous and non-Indigenous architects</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-565275</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">OTHER STUDIES IN HUMAN SOCIETY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms TS Mallie; Asst Prof NA Blair; Dr S Fleming
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 16,000.00
Application Year: 2006
First Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This cross-disciplinary approach of Architecture and Aboriginal Studies creates a new field when combined with decolonising methodology. This study aims to acquire knowledge and to consider the racial identities of the architect designer and building user. It is expected to lead to an improved understanding of architecture and the built environment for building users in Indigenous communities and organisations. It will also add further depth to Australian architectural design.</description>
      <description type="brief">This is a qualitative research project that is based on the Indigenous Research Methodology of 'reframing' (Smith, 1999: 153-4) to present an Indigenous perspective. It is the first time that Indigenous architect's voices have been brought together in a form that will engage and benefit those in the emerging field of Indigenous architecture, where their voices and experiences have hitherto been marginalised. There are very few Indigenous architects in Australia and this is an opportunity to present their voices and experiences. The ultimate outcome is a Master of Philosophy.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0453648</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0453648</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0453648</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Modelling of coupled heat and water flow through layered soils with an extension to heat flow through granulated soils</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-465942</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">MATHEMATICS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr CJ Matthews; Dr RD Braddock; Dr FJ Cook; Dr JH Knight
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 144,184.00
Application Year: 2003
First Year: 2004
</description>
      <description type="brief">The main aim of this project is to develop a mathematical model to simulate coupled heat and water flow through layered soils. The coupling of the two processes will allow us to examine the interaction between heat and water flow. The project also aims to extend the heat component of the flow model to granulated heterogeneous soils by developing a model that encapsulates heat effects at the microscopic and macroscopic level. The model will be applied to two problems 1) hydraulic barriers in cover liner designs for landfills and 2) assessing the ability of heat sensors to measure various soil properties under field conditions.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989113</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989113</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989113</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Rottnest Island as Black Prison and White Playground: A case study of the problems and prospects for Reconciliation in Australia</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-589763</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">OTHER STUDIES IN HUMAN SOCIETY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr GP Stasiuk; Mr L Collard; Prof CA McGarty; Dr KA Trees
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 100,000.00
Application Year: 2008
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Many Australians are committed to Reconciliation. This project seeks to build on this commitment by finding out why the attempts to establish appropriate commemoration of the deaths of hundreds of Aboriginal and boys in the Rottnest Island Prison up to 1931 have so far been unsuccessful. The project will uncover new ways to advance the cause of Reconciliation and will bring these to public attention in the form of a documentary film. Rottnest Island could continue to be a source of division and shame but it also has the potential to be unlocked as a source of national pride. </description>
      <description type="brief">This project will use the Aboriginal Prison on Rottnest Island as a specific site to explore and analyse the processes and problems associated with Reconciliation in Australia. It will weave political and social psychological analyses with documentary film making to uncover the factors that have blocked progress towards a culturally appropriate commemoration of the harm that was done to Aboriginal peoples and blocked appropriate protection of grave sites on the Island. The project will use this specific site to develop and disseminate ways for furthering the goals of Reconciliation.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348198</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348198</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348198</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre for Solar Energy Systems</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-595489</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">ENVIRONMENTAL ENGINEERING</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof AW BlakersDr KJ WeberDr MJ StocksDr PJ VerlindenProf PJ JenningsDr DH MacdonaldDr KM LovegroveDr GH JohnstonDr VA EverettDr JH BabaeiDr MJ KerrDr CP LundDr JC CornishDr TL Pryor
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Application Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">The National Centre of Excellence for Solar Energy Systems will be an international leader in research, commercialisation and education in the area of solar energy conversion. Research will be conducted into solar cell and solar thermal technologies, including thin crystalline and amorphous silicon solar cells that use far less silicon than conventional cells; systems that concentrate sunlight by 50-500 times; and very efficient solar cells for use in concentrator systems. Expected outcomes include long-term research, commercial research, publications, education, community outreach and commercialisation of solar energy technologies to benefit Australia's economy and environment.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100292</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100292</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100292</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Political history of the New South Wales Aboriginal Land Rights Act, 1983</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-502828</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">POLICY AND ADMINISTRATION</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms Heidi Norman; Prof Gillian K Cowlishaw; Prof Jock H Collins; Prof Heather Goodall
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 103,236.00
Application Year: 2009
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">The story of the Aboriginal Land Rights Act (ALRA) that established the land councils, made provisions for land recovery and enterprises, and reshaped Aboriginal people's relationship with the state has not been told.  The ALRA initiated a new policy era of self-determination through the three-tier Aboriginal Land Council Network mechanism for land recovery and 15 year compensation fund to support the network and develop enterprises.  Aboriginal Land Councils have become significant land holders - 81367 hectares valued at over $2billion and investment.  The story of the ALRA is one of tenacious engagement with the state and one of tradition and change that has not been documented.</description>
      <description type="brief">This study is the first political history of the NSW Aboriginal Land Rights Act (1983) (ALRA). Further to earlier studies of land demands in NSW, this study highlights the period from 1972 through to 2004. This period covers the heightened movement for land rights recognition, the Government's Inquiry, subsequent legislation establishing the three tier land council network and the activities of the land council including administrative, land recovery, enterprise development and community services and development. The study makes a significant contribution to policy debates, and understanding more broadly the possibilities and limits of state based land rights regimes and Aboriginal self-determination.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0347913</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0347913</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0347913</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Teaching Aboriginal Studies: A Critical Analysis of Core Aboriginal Studies Subjects in Primary Teacher Education Courses.</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-485355</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">EDUCATION STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms J Mooney A/Prof RG Craven A/Prof C Halse
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 20,000.00
Application Year: 2002
First Year: 2003
</description>
      <description type="brief">The effective teaching of Aboriginal Studies in primary schools is an important tool for achieving Reconciliation, and mutual respect and understanding between Aboriginal and non-Aboriginal Australians. This cannot be achieved without effective teacher education. This study aims to: identify successful features of core Aboriginal Studies teacher education courses that can be emulated by teacher education institutions; and to critically analyse the nature, success and impact of core Aboriginal Studies primary teacher education courses upon primary preservice teachers? commitment and ability to teach Aboriginal Studies in schools.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775819</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775819</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775819</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Investigating the source of arsenic contamination in the Bogong Moth and the impacts on the ecology of the Australian alps.</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-496332</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">ECOLOGY AND EVOLUTION</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms P Love; Dr S Lawler
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 109,701.00
Application Year: 2006
First Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">Much of Australias alpine region is National Park and as such, is managed for the conservation of its unique fauna and flora. The recent discovery of Arsenic in the Bogong Moth and one of its key predators, the endangered Pygmy Possum, raises questions about how to manage this threat to this unique ecosystem. Two main concerns are the preservation of the Bogong Moth, as an Indigenous Icon, and the conservation of the Pygmy Possum. In order to manage this threat we need to identify how, when and where the Bogong Moth is exposed to Arsenic. This information will aid in conserving the unique alpine species, including the Mountain Pygmy Possum, and protecting the Indigenous value of the Moth.  </description>
      <description type="brief">The contamination of the Bogong Moth, at the bottom of the food web with Arsenic puts many endemic species at risk, as Arsenic accumulates within the food web. Sub-lethal quantities of Arsenic can cause cancer, mutation and birth defects, and ultimately increases the likelihood of extinction in endangered species. The aim of this research is to identify the source of the Arsenic which contaminates the Bogong Moth. This will aid in the prevention of contamination of the Bogong Moth, the alpine ecosystem and enhance the survival of its unique species.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775828</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775828</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775828</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">A study of Buddhism and Chinese Buddhist Monks in modernising China</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-595489</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">RELIGION AND RELIGIOUS TRADITIONS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr RP Shaw; Dr BD Penny
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 12,373.00
Application Year: 2006
First Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This project will analyse the relationship between religion and modernisation in China. There is a tendency for modernising states to abandon or marginalise traditional religions but paradoxically, while religious practice has undergone transformation and reform in China, Buddhism has not only survived but flourished over the last two decades. This project will investigate these changes and will assist in broadening the fields of expertise in the vibrant and growing field of Buddhist studies within Australia, a development that will undoubtedly help to forge closer links in the region, both in academic forums and more broadly with informal people-to-people contact.</description>
      <description type="brief">I will analyse the relationship of religion and modernity in China - how traditional religion and eminent religious figures are represented historically and in contemporary China. The theme of hagiographic invention and 'pattern' versus 'particular' will be addressed as will the state of Buddhism during the late Qing and the Republican period, and the historical genealogical lineages of eminent Buddhist monks. There is a tendency for modernising states to abandon or marginalise traditional religions but paradoxically, while religious practice has undergone transformation and reform, in the case of Chinese Buddhism it has not only survived but has flourished over the last two decades. This project seeks to shed light on this phenomenon.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348165</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:58Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348165</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348165</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre for Complex Dynamic Systems and Control</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-565275</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">MANUFACTURING ENGINEERING</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof RH MiddletonProf GC GoodwinProf M FuProf KL MengersenProf I RaeburnA/Prof BM NinnessDr SO MoheimaniDr WP HeathDr RO WattsDr JH BraslavskyDr JA De DonaDr R GerlachDr MM SeronA/Prof B SimsDr SR WellerDr GA WillisDr S CrisafulliDr SA DomantiDr AA Shook
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 13,749,290.00
Application Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">Complex dynamic systems are an inescapable feature of the world we live in. Modelling, analysing and optimizing complex behaviour is crucial for environment, process industry, biomedical, energy distribution, transportation and other applications. The Centre for Complex Dynamic Systems and Control will become an international authority in the analysis, design and optimization of complex dynamic systems, pursuing both outstanding fundamental and cutting edge applied research outcomes. These outcomes will be of specific benefit to partner organizations including minerals, process, metal forming, and automotive industries.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208035</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208035</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208035</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Models of Knowledge Restructuring</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-464686</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">PSYCHOLOGY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof S Lewandowsky Dr ML Kalish
Scheme: Discovery Projects
Funding: $AUD 150,000.00
Application Year: 2001
First Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">In a world of rapid change, people must frequently adapt cognitive skills to new technologies. This often requires restructuring of knowledge, from simple initial strategies to increasingly complex ways of mastering the task. This is not always easy and people sometimes resist knowledge restructuring. We present a network model of knowledge restructuring that combines attentional processes with error-driven learning. The model accounts for several existing results and makes predictions that guide the proposed research. Three factors will be examined empirically: (1) the role of directing attention to alternative strategies; (2) the imperfection of existing knowledge; and (3) the complexity of alternative strategies.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348178</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:56Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348178</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="program">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/CE0348178</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">ARC Centre of Excellence for Quantum-Atom Optics</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-595489</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">ATOMIC AND MOLECULAR PHYSICS; NUCLEAR AND PARTICLE PHYSICS; PLASMA PHYSICS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Prof HA BachorDr KG BaldwinDr JD CloseDr JJ HopeProf YS KivsharDr P LamDr EA OstrovskayaDr CM SavageDr AG TruscottDr JF CorneyDr MJ DavisProf PD DrummondDr KV KheruntsyanDr MD ReidA/Prof BJ DaltonProf P HannafordProf TD KieuProf R McLeanDr WJ Rowlands
Scheme: ARC Centres of Excellence
Funding: $AUD 16,950,000.00
Application Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">The Centre will combine pre-eminent Australian theoretical and experimental research groups in quantum and atom optics to create a powerful network to advance the rapidly developing field of Quantum-Atom Optics. We will exploit the quantum nature of multiple particle quantum states of atoms and photons including entangled light and Bose-Einstein condensates. The Centre will focus on fundamental research, but our long term goal is to underpin and develop the next generation quantum technology. We aim to build a quantum toolbox to enable applications such as the transfer and storage of information for photonics, and precision quantum control of atoms for enhanced atom interferometry.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989056</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989056</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0989056</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Adoption and Effective Use of Information Communication Technologies in Indigenous Communities in Australia</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-595489</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">INFORMATION SYSTEMS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mr PJ Radoll; Prof KR Jacobs; Dr WD Fernandez; Dr BH Hunter; Prof M Dodson
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 30,000.00
Application Year: 2008
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This project on Indigenous use of the internet aims to identify the reasons why Indigenous Australians are 69% less likely to access the Internet than their non-Indigenous counterparts as demonstrated in the last census. This research will assist in innovative policy development including the creation of a culturally-sensitive model to assist Indigenous communities to raise their use of computers and the internet. Ultimately the aim of the research is to provide mechanisms to engage Indigenous people with current technology to advance health, education and housing outcomes in their communities. </description>
      <description type="brief">This timely project is a study of the low engagement levels of Indigenous Australians with the internet, which links financial, educational, government and non-government services to Australian households. Both the 2001 and 2006 Census' demonstrate that Indigenous Australians are 69% less likely to access the Internet than the rest of the Australian population. Previous research confirms that income and education affects computer and internet use. This project seeks to identify characteristics of Indigenous communities that create barriers to internet usage. The research aims to explain the gap in adoption and to suggest areas in which government policy can assist Indigenous communities in removing barriers to internet engagement.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775837</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775837</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0775837</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">A study of how Aboriginal women fare in liberal democracies</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-502828</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">LAW</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms MJ Davis; Prof Dr LY Behrendt
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 12,000.00
Application Year: 2006
First Year: 2007
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This study of how Aboriginal women fare in liberal democracies will contribute to a better understanding of the challenges faced by Aboriginal women in Australia.  The survival of Aboriginal culture and the health and well being of Aboriginal children depend on the health of Aboriginal women.  A deeper understanding of the institutional difficulties faced by Aboriginal women within Indigenous communities as well as Australia's public institutions will contribute to strengthening Australia's social and economic fabric.   </description>
      <description type="brief">This study aims to examine how Aboriginal women are faring in Australian liberal democracy by comparing the record of Australia's public institutions with that of Canada's public institutions. This study aims to fill a significant gap in the literature assessing how liberal democracies treat Aboriginal women. The study aims to contribute to the national debate about reform of Australia's public institutions by making an argument for greater inclusiveness of Aboriginal women.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100297</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:57Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100297</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI100100297</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Archaeology in the long grass: A study of Aboriginal fringe camp sites in the urban hinterland around Darwin, Australia</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-593299</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">ARCHAEOLOGY</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Ms Kellie L Pollard; A/Prof Claire E Smith; A/Prof Heather D Burke
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 158,000.00
Application Year: 2009
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">This research will contribute to the priority goal of strengthening Australia's social and economic fabric by: 1) advancing the government priority policy commitment to close the gap of Indigenous disadvantage by contributing to social and economic improvements for Indigenous people living in the long grass around Darwin, and other urban centres; 2) contributing to native title debates; 3) developing the research capacity of Indigenous Australians; and 4) increasing public understandings of Aboriginal culture. The Larrakia Nation Aboriginal Corporation will benefit from enhanced research capacity through the quality training of research associates and new data to inform policy decisions and recommendations.</description>
      <description type="brief">This collaborative project with the Larrakia Nation Aboriginal Corporation will analyse Aboriginal fringe campsites or &#x2018;contact period&#x2019; sites in the urban hinterland around Darwin. The aim is to understand the adaptive strategies of Aboriginal people during a major period of transformation. Methods include archaeological surveys and excavations, analyzing historical documents and collecting oral histories. Project outputs include a doctoral thesis in contact archaeology, cultural maps of Aboriginal landuse across space and through time, new data to inform policy decisions and recommendations by the Larrakia Nation, interpretative materials for Larrakia tourism ventures, and the quality training of Larrakia research associates.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0560709</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:55Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0560709</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DI0560709</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">The Benefits of HSC Aboriginal Studies: Disentangling the Impact on Indigenous Students? Self-Concepts and Educational Outcomes</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-485355</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">EDUCATION STUDIES</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Mrs DE Wray; A/Prof RG Craven
Scheme: Discovery Indigenous Researchers Development
Funding: $AUD 38,631.00
Application Year: 2004
First Year: 2005
</description>
      <description type="Community Benefit">The HSC Aboriginal Studies course was introduced into NSW secondary schools in 1991 however the anticipated positive impact of this course on Indigenous students? self-concepts and educational outcomes has not been evaluated. This research aims to evaluate the impact of this course on Indigenous students? self-concepts and educational outcomes in order to: Identify strengths and limitations of this course as a basis of strengthening curriculum; identify new solutions for enhancing the tangible impact of this course on desirable educational outcomes for Indigenous students, and result in increasing Indigenous students? participation and retention in the HSC to predicate important further education, employment and life opportunities.</description>
      <description type="brief">Indigenous students are the most educationally disadvantaged Australians. The Aboriginal Studies HSC Course was introduced to enhance Indigenous students? self-concepts and educational outcomes. There is a paucity of research that has evaluated these aims. Capitalising on advances in educational psychology this investigation aims to: Test the impact of this course on Indigenous students? self-concepts, retention and educational outcomes; and elucidate course strengths and limitations. This will result in new solutions for enhancing the courses? impact on desirable educational outcomes for Indigenous students, strengthening curriculum, and distinguishing effective theory and research of salience to Indigenous students.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <record>
      <header>
        <identifier>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208039</identifier>
        <datestamp>2011-09-27T05:40:54Z</datestamp>
        <setSpec>class:activity</setSpec>
        <setSpec>group:Australian0x20Research0x20Council</setSpec>
        <setSpec>dataSource:AU_RESEARCH_GRANTS</setSpec>
      </header>
      <metadata>
        <registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.3/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Research Council">
    <key>http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208039</key>
    <originatingSource>arc.gov.au</originatingSource>
    <activity type="project">
      <identifier type="purl">http://purl.org/au-research/grants/arc/DP0208039</identifier>
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart type="full">Data Adaptive Geophysical Inversion</namePart>
      </name>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-627854</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>http://nla.gov.au/nla.party-536838</key>
        <relation type="isFundedBy">
        </relation>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="local">GEOPHYSICS</subject>
      <description type="notes">Investigators: Dr M Sambridge Prof B Kennett
Scheme: Discovery Projects
Funding: $AUD 208,000.00
Application Year: 2001
First Year: 2002
</description>
      <description type="brief">The goal of this project is to develop new techniques for extracting information about the interior structure of the Earth from large geophysical data sets. These methods will be adaptive so that they allow the definition of the physical model to be constrained by the character of the data. The project will utilize advances in computational geometry, nonlinear inversion and interactive computer visualisation to extract robust information from data sets with variable resolving power. The resulting algorithms will be applicable to a wide range of problems in the physical sciences.</description>
    </activity>
  </registryObject>
        </registryObjects>
      </metadata>
    </record>
    <resumptionToken expirationDate="2012-05-15T03:34:20Z" completeListSize="14004" cursor="0">0887D571F5CCB60BA08D9126DA94EDAD1FDCEE1F</resumptionToken>
  </ListRecords>
</OAI-PMH>
